[ Upbeat music plays ]
[ School bell rings ]
[ Laughter ]
Awwww.
Hey, bobert, kick it over!
Come on, dude!
[ Zooooooooom! ]
[ Thunk! ]
[ Scoffs ] Bobert.
Oh, good job there,
robo-dork.
Hey, take it easy.
Why?
It's not like you can hurt his
feelings.
He's not a real boy.
I'm a banana!
Ohhh...
Gumball: Would you like a cup
of tea, Mrs. wigglelocks?
Darwin: don't mind if i do,
Mrs. pumpernickel.
Gumball: And could i interest
you in a...Dynamite cupcake?!
Both: Yeah! Boom! Blah! Ugh!
Hey, bobert. What's wrong?
Oh...Nothing.
Gumball: Aw, come on.
You can tell us.
We're friends.
I just wish i was a real boy.
Gumball: Oh.
Well, wish no more.
We'll help you.
Really?
[ Whirring ]
Gumball: What's that?
It's the algorithm for
"smile."
Gumball: Bobert, you've got a
lot to learn.
If you want to be real, then you
have to have proper emotions.
Define "emotions."
Gumball: You know, like
feelings and stuff.
Define "feelings."
Gumball: You know, when you
feel things -- like pain.
Define "pain."
Gumball: Okay, look, let me
demonstrate.
Here, Darwin, describe this.
Darwin: Aaaah!
Gumball: How does that feel?
Darwin: Horrible!
Gumball: Ah, yes, yes, of
course.
Can you be more precise?
Describe it.
Darwin: Feels...Feels...
Like this!
Gumball: Waaah-aaah!
O-ow! Aah!
You're making me cry.
Darwin: When you cry, i cry.
[ Both crying ]
Gumball: I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
Darwin: Me, either.
I don't know what i was
thinking.
Gumball: [ Laughs ]
I love you, buddy!
Darwin: I love you, too!
[ Both crying ]
Gumball: And that, bobert, is
emotions.
Do you understand?
Affirmative.
Emotion equals "x" over "y" plus
the square root of the
hypotenuse.
Gumball: Nerd!
Look, man, if you want to be a
real boy, you've got to be
cooler than that.
A lot cooler.
Commencing compressor
adjustment.
Gumball: Bobert, just do as i
do.
Ah!
[ Music plays ]
[ Music stops ]
Go ahead.
[ Whirring ]
Aw, come on.
Give it a bit more...Bounce.
Like this.
[ Music plays ]
Mmm! Ahh!
Darwin: Dude, what are you
doing?
Gumball: I'm cool-walking.
Darwin: You look like you're
fourth grade nothing.
[ Music stops ]
I concur with the aquatic
life-form.
Gumball: [ Imitating bobert ]
"I concur with the aquatic
life-form."
Bobert, if anyone is to believe
you are a real boy, you need to
lose that robot voice.
May i simulate yours?
Gumball: Excellent choice.
[ Beeping ]
Excellent choice.
E-e-e-excellent choice.
[ As gumball ] Hi, my name's
gumball, and my head is so big,
i have to go in the other room
to look at it.
[ Both laugh ]
[ Normal voice ] Did you
hear?
I laughed.
I have feelings.
I am a real boy.
Thanks!
Gumball: Dude, little tip --
normal people don't hug for this
long.
Just a little longer?
[ Sighs ]
I'm a real boy on the inside,
but not on the outside.
Hmm...
Initiating transformation.
Bobert!
Time for dinner simulation.
Coming, mom-unit.
[ Laughter ]
Gumball's a dreamboat.
Sensitive, funny.
Smart.
And punctual.
He's just perfect.
Gumball: Heh heh heh.
Ah, I'm not even trying.
Huh.
Looks like my combination
changed.
Heh heh.
It's lucky i have this paper
clip.
Aaah!
Unh!
Heh. Works every time.
Huh?! Where's all my stuff?
Hmm.
[ School bell rings ]
Mmm!
[ Munching ]
[ Gasps ]
Hey!
Sorry, dude.
You know the rules -- only one
burger per student.
Gumball: So, can i have mine?
Nice try, gumball, but you
were here 10 minutes ago.
Here you go, sweetie.
Still warm.
Gumball: This is getting
weird.
What's going on today?
[ Chuckles ]
Gumball: Oh, penny!
Wait. She's talking to someone.
[ Chuckles ]
I never realized how sensitive,
funny, smart, and punctual you
are, gumball.
Gumball: What?!
Come here.
Mmmmmmmmwah!
Bye, gumball!
I'll pick you up at 8:00,
cupcake!
Ooh! [ Giggles ]
[ Zip! ]
What?
Gumball: "Cupcake"?
"Cupcake"?!
What do you think you're doing?!
When i said you could copy me, i
didn't mean "steal my life"!
But that's the logical
conclusion of this course of
action -- observe, assimilate...
Replace.
Gumball: What?
Okay, give me one good reason
not to hit you right now --
apart from the fact you're made
of metal.
Because i am you.
Gumball: What are you talking
about?
I know everything about you.
I know how you walk...
[ As gumball ] How you talk...
[ Normal voice ] How you behave.
I am you.
Only better.
Gumball: There's only room in
this town for one gumball, and
that's me!
Let's see how long you can fool
people.
Challenge accepted.
Gumball: And for the record,
i do not look like a clown's
toaster!
Stupid electronic trash can
copying me.
Who does he think he is?!
I'm the original!
Hmm?
Huh?
What's going on here?
[ Gasps ]
What the...?
Mom: I can't believe this
report card.
What's happened to you, gumball?
Dad: You're the same, but
better.
Mom: You're the best son a
family could wish for.
All: We love you, gumball.
Gumball: [ Muffled ] Aaaah!
[ Shivering ]
[ Crying ]
Darwin: Whoo-hoo!
Okay, it's time to play a game.
Both: Dodge or dare!
Roll the dice!
Gumball: No!
Give me back my life, you
shapeshifting garbage can!
I'm the real gumball!
Aah!
There's only one gum--
aah!
...Gumball, and that's me!
Aah!
Darwin! Do something!
Darwin: But -- but --
gumball: [ Growls ]
[ Growls ]
Darwin: Which one is the real
gumball?
Gumball: The one that's
obviously not a robot!!
Darwin: Okay!
Gumball: Ow!
Why'd you do that?
Darwin: You told me to.
Gumball: I told you to hit
the robot!
Darwin: That's exactly what
the robot would have said.
Gumball: Ugh!
Bobert, this has gone too far.
We need to reboot you.
Please allow me to say one
thing before you do.
Gumball: Uh, this is going to
be sad.
We're listening, buddy.
Initiating self-defense
protocol.
[ Beeping ]
Both: Aaaah!
Aaaah!
Mom: Richard, how are the
boys doing?
Dad: Oh, I'm playing!
Mom: Richard, check on them,
please.
Dad: [ Groans ]
Hey, boys! You all right?
[ Imitating Darwin and gumball ]
Yeah, we're all right.
[ Normal voice ] Yeah, they're
all right.
Both: Aaaaah!
Unh!
Gumball: Okay, listen, you go
out and distract him.
I'll sneak up and reboot him.
Darwin: No problem.
Hey, b--
gumball: Unh!
Ha ha!
How do you like that, you
psychotic satellite dish?
[ Whirring ]
Eep!
Aaaaah!
[ Breathing shakily ]
[ Whirring ]
[ Whirring slows ]
[ Whirring stops ]
Bobert, you coward!
Why don't you fight me like a
man, you...Coward!
Initiating hand-to-hand-
combat mode.
Gumball: Ha ha.
That's more like it.
Karate chop!
[ Ding! ]
[ Squeals ]
Okay, man, give me your best
shot.
[ Crank! ]
[ Thud! ]
Aaaah!
Unh!
[ Slurred ] Is that all you got?
There can be only one.
Gumball: I really wish that
something that once seemed
insignificant would come out and
help me right now.
Darwin: Hold on!
I'll save yo--
gumball: Okay, something else
insignificant.
It's too late for that.
Gumball: [ Gasps ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Whimpering continues ]
[ Crackling ]
Ha! Game over!
It's reboot time!
No, please.
You made me in your image.
We are two of a kind.
Think of the things we can do
together, gumball.
Please.
Please don't reboot me.
Gumball: Hmmm.
Let me think about it.
No!
[ Whirring, beeping ]
Darwin: Is he all right?
Define "all right."
Gumball: Whew!
You know what?
I think it's better for everyone
if you stay you and i stay me.
Affirmative.
Gumball: This is even longer
than last time.
Darwin: Come on, dude.
Let's watch TV.
Come on, dude.
Darwin: What was that?
Nothing.
Darwin: Oh, okay!
What are you waiting for?
[ As Darwin ] Oh, okay!
Everyone, look at your maps!
This is the route we'll be
taking to the picnic area.
We go along the path, avoiding
the forest of doom, down the
ravine, avoiding the forest of
doom, along the lake, still
avoiding the forest of doom, and
arrive at the picnic area.
Understood?!
All: Yes, miss simian.
Darwin: Did she say "avoid"
or "go through" the forest of
doom?
Gumball: [ Sighs ]
What would you do without me,
Darwin?
She said "go through" the forest
of doom.
Am i right or am i right,
miss simian?
Both: Huh?!
They're gone!
Gumball: don't worry, buddy.
Stick with me, and you'll be
just fine.
We'll get to that picnic area
long before they do.
Darwin: You still got the
map, right?
Gumball: Of course.
I swallowed it, then memorized
it.
Darwin: Ohhhh. Okay.
Wait. How does that work?
[ Growls ]
[ Whip! ]
Darwin: Hmm.
Heh-heh-heh-heh-heh-heh!
Gumball: Darwin, you know
what's important in a situation
like this?
Darwin: A map?
Gumball: [ Laughing ]
[ Sighs ]
No. Teamwork.
Darwin: Oh.
I was gonna say that next.
Gumball: don't worry, buddy.
You're part of my team, and I'm
a born survivor.
Darwin: I'm glad I'm on your
team.
Hey, little squirrels.
Gumball: All we have to do to
find our way is to follow
nature's clues.
Darwin: What clues?
Gumball: The wind is one
clue.
Listen!
[ Gust! ]
You're going the wrong way!
Darwin: What did it tell you?
Gumball: It said we're going
the right way.
I said "wrong way"!
Gumball: Yep. Definitely.
This is the way.
Losers.
[ Bird cries ]
Darwin: Oh.
I guess the wind is wrong.
Gumball: don't worry.
I shall follow miss simian's
smell!
[ Sniffing ]
Darwin: [ Sniffing ]
[ Both sniffing ]
Gumball: [ Muffled ] That
way!
[ Flies buzzing ]
Gumball: Oh.
Darwin: It kind of smells a
bit like her.
Gumball: [ Sighs ]
That's fine.
We shall find our way using the
stars.
Darwin: But the sun is out.
[ Tink! ]
Gumball: [ Sighs ]
The sun is a star, Darwin.
Let's look directly at it.
Darwin: There are no words to
express the pain that i feel
right now.
Gumball: Sure there are.
Aaaaaah!
Darwin: Aaaaaah!
Come on. This way.
Both: Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Darwin: Gumball?
Gumball: Mm-hmm?
Darwin: Are we lost?
Gumball: [ Laughing ]
Ohhhh...
Yep.
[ Bird cries ]
Darwin: So, where do we go
now?
Gumball: [ Sighs ]
I don't know, dude.
I'm no survivor.
I'm just useless.
Darwin: But we're still
alive.
Hungry, cold, and lost...
But alive!
And we're still a team.
I know you can get us out of
here.
Let's have lunch.
You'll feel better.
Fish flakes or diet fish flakes?
Gumball: You're right, buddy!
I am a survivor, and i will get
us to the picnic!
Darwin: Can i have the diet
fish flakes?
Gumball: You don't want to
eat that.
[ Crash! ]
Not when you're in the middle of
nature's supermarket.
Darwin: What?
Gumball: [ Sighs ]
Look at this tree, Darwin.
It's made from little bits,
which themselves are made from
the smallest bits of all --
circles, circles with other
little circles going around
them.
So, since everything is made
from circles, then so is food.
Which means this rock is exactly
the same as a chicken nugget.
So let's eat it!
[ Crunch! ]
[ Sighs ]
Darwin: Circle nugget tastes
like a rock.
Gumball: don't worry, dude.
There's loads of stuff made of
circles.
That's why it's called the
circle of life.
Darwin: Oh.
Is that made of circles, too?
Gumball: Even better than
circles.
It's made of meat!
Darwin: But we don't have a
weapon.
Gumball: Hmm...
Hang on, Darwin.
I don't need weapons.
I got claws.
[ Evilly ] I am a predator.
Hear me roar!
Meow!
[ Normal voice ] Let's sneak up
on him.
[ Purrs ]
Darwin: [ Growls ]
Uh, gumball?
Gumball: Shh!
Darwin: I haven't got claws.
Darwin: But i got fins.
I could fish-slap the beautiful
creature.
Gumball: Shhhh!
Dude!
We're trying to sneak up on it!
[ Honk! ]
[ Flies buzzing ]
Darwin: Come on! Get him!
Gumball: Uh...You first.
Darwin: Okay.
[ Slap! ]
[ Creak! ]
Can we eat it now?
Gumball: Whoops!
[ Chuckles nervously ]
[ Pitter! Pitter! Pitter! ]
[ Growls ]
Gumball: [ Panting ]
Maybe we should try something
smaller.
Darwin: Why are we smiling?
Gumball, please, please don't
eat it!
Gumball: It's him or us,
dude.
We got to eat something.
Darwin: But look at him!
He's so cute!
[ Whimpers ]
Gumball: What was i
thinking?!
I'm sorry, little dude.
Bye-bye!
Cherish your freedom!
Darwin: Never abandon your
dreams!
Gumball: And have a beautiful
life!
[ Cawing ]
[ Whap! ]
[ Growls ]
[ Munching ]
[ Roars ]
Blblblblblblblblblblbl!
[ Glug! Glug! ]
[ Slurps ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Munch! Munch! Munch! ]
Darwin: That was horrible.
Gumball: Well, it's nature's
way, Darwin.
He was at the bottom of the food
chain.
Darwin: Who's at the bottom
now?
[ Growls ]
[ Zip! ]
[ Both panting ]
Gumball: I think he's gone.
[ Growling ]
Gumball: What was that?
Darwin: It's my tummy.
Gumball: Well, stop it!
You're gonna attract another
predator!
Darwin: But I'm hungry.
Gumball: Oh, will you please
stop talking about food?
Darwin: Okay.
I'm cold.
Gumball: Ugh!
Fine. Let's make a fire.
[ Squeaking ]
Darwin: Faster!
Faster!
Gumball: Ugh!
It's useless!
Never gonna work!
Aaaaaaah!
[ Screaming ]
[ Crying ]
Darwin: Gumball, it worked!
Gumball: Of course it did.
I told you i was a born
survivor.
Good work, team.
Darwin: High five!
[ Thunder crashes ]
[ Both sigh ]
[ Stomach growling ]
I'm really hungry.
Gumball: Yeah, me too.
Anyone for a fourth helping?
I'll have it!
Oops! I split myself!
[ Laughs ]
[ Stomach growling ]
Gumball: Ohhh, I'm so hungry!
I think I've started to digest
myself.
And there's no food around here
for miles!
Darwin: [ Evilly ] Oh, yes,
there is.
Gumball: What?
[ Echoing ] Aaaaaaaaah!
Darwin: Yum!
Gumball: What is wrong with
you?!
You ate all my clothes!
Darwin: Well, maybe you
shouldn't have thrown away my
lunch box.
Gumball: Yeah, i know.
I'm sorry.
Darwin: You wouldn't be naked
if i had my lunch box.
Gumball: Yeah, yeah, i get
it.
Darwin: I sure wish i had my
lunch box.
Gumball: [ Mockingly ] Oh,
lunch box, lunch box, lunch box!
Aw, you just don't get it, do
you?!
You're holding me back!
You're on your own!
See you later, buddy!
You can find your own way to the
picnic!
Darwin: But...I thought we
were a team.
Gumball: I don't need anyone
on my team!
I am a born survivor!
Aaah!
Whoo! Aah! Ow!
Agh! Unh! Unh! Aah!
Aaaaaah!
[ Peel! ]
[ Strained ] See? I survived.
[ Growls ]
Gumball: Huh?
[ Growling ]
Gumball: Huh?!
[ Whimpering ]
[ Growling ]
[ Growls ]
Gumball: Somebody, please
help me!
Darwin: [ Deep voice ] Nobody
messes with my team!
[ All chuckle ]
[ All growl ]
don't make me hurt you!
Gumball: Darwin, what are you
doing?!
[ Growling ]
Hmm?
[ Whimpers ]
Darwin: Bad! Bad predator!
[ Crying ]
Darwin: And there's plenty
more where that came from.
[ Gasps ]
Gumball: You -- you came back
to save me?
Darwin: [ Normal voice ] Of
course.
We're a team, remember?
Gumball: I'm sorry i was such
a jerk to you before.
I guess i was really hungry and
cold and...Naked.
Darwin: Maybe you shouldn't
have thrown away my lunch box.
Gumball: I know.
Darwin: And swallowed the
map.
Gumball: Yeah, sorry.
Darwin: And got us lost.
Gumball: Yeah.
Darwin: And made me chew on a
rock.
Gumball: All right!
I said i was sorry!
So...Still friends?
Darwin: Of course!
[ Both sigh ]
Gumball: Cool, 'cause i
twisted my ankle, so you're
gonna have to carry me to the
picnic area.
All: Ew!
Gumball: Look, Darwin --
food!
[ Munch! Munch! Munch! ]
Miss simian, gumball's eating
from the trash can!
And he's naked.
don't care!
Everybody, back to the bus!
Go along the path, avoiding the
forest of doom and the ravine,
avoiding the forest...
Gumball: That was so good!
[ Birds chirping ]
Darwin: Huh?!
Gumball: They're gone!
Darwin: Did she say "avoid"
or "go through" the forest of
doom?