Class! Time to hand in your homework!
What are we gonna do?
If we tell her the truth, she'll flip!
Be cool, buddy. It'll be fine.
At least it's on time.
I wasn't built to take this much pressure!
Relax, man.
We'll just tell her what really happened.
All right, you two.
What's today's excuse?
Our dad ate our homework. Rrrrrrrrrrr...
Go to the guidance counselor immediately!
But, miss simian...
and don't come back until
you've learned how to tell the truth!
And this is what the inside
of a liar looks like. Ewwww!
Notice the dark abyss here.
That's the corrupt soul of the liar.
But, Mr. small, we're not liars.
You should tell that to the last
boy that sat there and lied to me.
He's there now.
The prison?! No, next to it.
The cemetery!
What happened to him?
He just works there.
Now, let me show you something.
This is the lying hat.
Now, watch what happens when i
put it on. Your mother called.
She says she hates you.
She does? I think my heart just broke.
It's okay, kids.
That was a lie.
But, you see, that's what a lie
will do... hurt your feelings.
She hates you.
She loves you. Yay! >> Hates you!
Aww. >> Loves you. Yay!
Hates you. Loves you.
Hatesyoulovesyouhatesyoulovesyou
hatesyoulovesyouhatesyoulovesyou
so, what have we learned today?
Never trust a man in
a hat. Yes, but what else?
Uhhhh... >> Honesty is the best policy.
Say it. Honesty is the best policy.
Good. And again.
Honesty is the best policy.
Honesty is the best policy...
Okay, Darwin.
Remember, from now on, we only
tell the truth. Okay.
Your face is too big.
Well, when you say "s,"
your gills whistle. You
smell so stinky,
sailors sing sea shanties about your
stinkyness! When you're asleep,
your face looks like this!
When you're awake,
You walk like a Princess!
You walk like a pigeon!
Okay. That's us covered.
Let's bring our honesty to the world.
You've got a
monobrow. You've got no hands.
Just being honest.
Your face is burnt. I love you.
But he'll never make the first move.
He's having a party
on Friday, and he didn't invite
you. >> What?! >> Sorry, man.
You're just not cool enough. Whoa-ho!
This one is long overdue. Hey, Tina?
You smell, and it's not very ladylike.
It's like a sweaty
watch strap. Nah, it's more like
raw chicken and rancid
milk in a plastic bag.
Yeah...
that's been left in the sun for a week.
Okay,
now that we have your smelliness covered,
let's move on to your personality.
Yep. The truth hurts.
Nigel. Let's leave all this behind
and go and live on a desert island.
But how would we survive?
On fruit, water... And love.
Did you ask us in here for a reason?
Yes, of course, watterson.
I've been getting a lot of
complaints.
What on earth's gotten into you?
Principal brown, can i be honest with you?
i... y-yes.
I can't help thinking
that your relationship
with miss simian could
be compromising your
professionalism.
I completely agree, gumball.
And, frankly,
i fear my education is suffering as a
result.
And besides, principal brown, you could do
so-o-o much better than that. Rrrrrrrrrr!
Okay, so you got honesty wrong.
Perhaps we should try something else.
I'd like you to meet a friend of mine.
One second.
Hello, children.
I'm the honesty bear. O-Kay.
I'm here to explain that
honesty's not all black and
white. But, like my fur,
it's more of a gray area.
Gray. See that? Gray fur.
Now, there are some things that
are "too" honest to say out
loud. Honesty bear, I'm confused.
What can we be honest about?
Let me put this in a language
you kids will understand...
hippity rap! H-h-h-h-honesty!!
Honesty! Break it down!
♪ when you want to
be honest, just beware ♪
♪ truth hurts in this
nitrogenic atmosphere ♪
♪ you got to wake up,
realize, and recognize ♪
♪ sometimes the truth
has strategical lies ♪
♪ but keep them lies
of a manageable size ♪
♪ or tears will arise
and hurt their eyes ♪
♪ so before you speak,
it's best to remember ♪
each individual case will
require a specific judgment
call, depending on who you're
talking to and the context
of the conversation!
Any questions? No? Excellent! Goodbye.
Okay, i think i got it.
You should always tell the
truth, unless you have to lie,
but if you do lie, you should
tell the truth about it, unless
you're talking to someone who's
lying, because if they tell
a lie and you tell the truth,
it'll be a lie because you were
lying about telling the truth,
inside of a lie, so the whole
thing's a lie while still being true.
Man,
this "truth and honesty" thing is hard.
Has anyone seen the nurse?
I think my head may be on fire.
Is my head on fire?
Um... W-would it be a good thing or a
bad thing if it was on fire?
A bad thing, of course!
It's not on fire.
For a minute there,
i thought my head was on fire.
What a relief.
So, how are things with you,
watterson?...Yeah, not bad. You?
Pretty good, pretty good.
So, no more of that lying
trouble, i hope? No.
>> All right, then. Toodle-oo!
Hmmmm. Okay. Looks I'm gonna have to
introduce you to someone else.
I'd like you to say hello
to the silence snake.
Hello, si... silencessssssssss!
B... silencessssssss!
Now, i bet your tiny minds are thinking...
"But what if
there's something important
we need to say? "Well, why don't
you ask the silence snake? Go on.
He won't bite. O-Kay...
What... silencesssssss!
Well, it looks like my work here is done.
W-w-whoa!
Aah! Boys? Can you hear me?
Say something!
I think my knees are
digging into my back.
You need to help me.
Now, there should be a little,
gold key on my desk. Don't worry!
I've got it here. Gosh.
Please, no! Wait! Maybe i can just...
Aaaaah! Okay, you need to get some help
right now. Right now! Elmore police.
Hello? Hello?
I'm sick of these prank phone calls.
It's just not the same. What now?
What's that supposed to mean? Nyeah! Unh!
What?! Miss simian's trapped down the
old abandoned well?!
I'm coming, my smoochkins! Hup! Aaaah!
E-elbows, don't fail me now.
So, anyway, the plan is to
live on fruit, water, and love.
Dude, i don't care.
Well,
go back to fixing the toilets, then!
What do you want? Nyeah!
What?! I'm trapped down the old
abandoned well?! No! I'm coming! Aaaaah!
Come on, chin. don't fail me now.
Whoa-oa-oa!
Slow down, little dudes. What's that?
Mr. small rocked back smugly on
his chair, fell into the bottom
drawer of his filing cabinet,
it locked shut, and you want to
use these crowbars to break him out?
Mmmmm. >> Aww. See ya!
Aah! Aah! Boys, i-i-is that you?
Do something! Anything!
Well, on the plus side, i think
that loosened the lock a little.
Keep going. Aah! Aah! Ooh! Aah!
Just a thought, but maybe you
want to lever the drawer
open with that crowbar.
Freeze! Police!
You're coming with me,
you little hooligans! But...
Why won't you talk? Talk, darn it! Talk!
Officer,
there's clearly been some kind of
misunderstanding.
Well, ma'am, looking at their
rap sheet, it seems they
are not first-time offenders.
Multiple counts of antisocial
behavior, vandalizing school property,
and setting their
principal on fire.
And all because you lied
about your father eating your homework.
Okay! I did it! Take me away! Why?
I thought it was gonna make me smart!
Well, it obviously didn't.
So,
i guess you boys didn't lie after all.
I'm so proud of you
two. Thanks, mom.
>> Um... One more thing.
You don't happen to know
where Mr. small is, do you?
The only clue we
could find was this sock.
Well. Case closed!
>> This isn't funny anymore!
Can somebody please open this thing?!
He-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-l...
Bowls... check! Spoons...
check! Cereal... check!
So much for easy opening!
It looks so simple on TV!
Man, i really don't want to go to school
today. Me neither. Let's not go!
You can do that? Sure! Hey, dad?
Yes? We really don't
want to go to school today.
Why? Are you sick? Nah.
We're just not up for it. Yeah!
School is boring!
But you have to go to school.
You're kids!
It's what you do! Aw! Ooh!
Mailman! Whoo-hoo!
I wish we were grown-ups, like dad.
Then we'd never have to go to
school and nobody
would tell us what to do.
We could drive trucks,
stay up all night, vote.
Vote... Finally! What's that?
Why? According to the fifth
amendment, i don't have to
answer that without my lawyer
present! Right.
Anyway, about school... Yeah.
You're kids, so you do what mom
tells me to tell you to do.
Being a kid is wretched-lame.
You should be happy to be young.
Before you know it,
you'll be overweight, unattractive,
balding, middle-aged.
Take over breakfast!
I don't want you to see me like this!
What's his problem?
You never know with that guy.
Come on. Let's have breakfast.
Man, what a pile of beans.
Dude, watch your language!
You'll get us in trouble!
Well, I'm sorry,
Darwin, but it is.
It's a big, steaming pile of beans.
Gumball, look! A shooting star!
This is our chance.
Make a wish! I wish i was a grown-up.
Me too! They don't work at all.
Faker! Darn kids!
What do you think you're doing?!
Today's lesson will be about
the transformations of the human body.
As you get older, hormones
begin to change your appearance. Here.
It's me as an adult talking to
my secretary over the intercom.
It's me voting! Awesome.
Passing notes, are we? No, miss simian.
Well, then, what's this?
That's us as adults?
I guess you're on topic, then.
Anyway, pimples...
Ew! Silence! Actually, it's pretty gross.
You may continue. Ewwwwww!
Pimples, or acne, can pop up
at any time...
Dude, what's that on your face?
What? What?! That. What?! It looks like a
greasy, yellow egg.
No, no, actually, it's more like
a small volcano with a sweaty golf ball.
Do something!
Do something! Okay, okay.
Hold on. Let me just, um...
I think we're gonna
need more little hats.
Aaaah! Relax, dude!
That's easy for you to say!
Why don't you have any?
Just lucky, i guess. Aaah!
Aaaaaah! Aaaaaaaaah! Ew!
I think that's all of them.
What's happening to us?
I think we've got the plague.
Do you have any
other symptoms?
My top lip feels a little silky.
Next comes the appearance
of hair on the body and face.
Dude, you look like an undercover cop.
Stop laughing! Do something! Okay.
I see mom do this all the time.
And dad, on one occasion.
That feels so much bet... aaaaaah!
Aah! don't worry, dude.
I'm not worried about me!
I'm worried about you!
You look like a baby werewolf!
No! Not me!
It was better when it was just you!
Guys, i don't mean to interrupt,
but this is the
girls' toilet. Yeah, sorry!
I got to sort this out.
Start chewing. Okay, settle down.
Everyone, get into your team for
dodgeball. No. Not dodgeball.
You're going down.
You get the idea. Please...
not above the should...
aah! Aah! Aah! The ear!
My ankle! Aah! A bowling ball?!
Catch! Enough!
Aaaaaah! Aaaaah!
This is horrible! We're monsters!
No, you're not. It's just a part of life.
Are you saying we're grown-ups now?
Apparently so.
Did you hear that?
That shooting star worked.
Now, get back to class!
All right, miss simian.
Wait a minute!
We don't have to listen to you anymore.
Because we're men!
♪ We're gonna test-drive a car ♪
♪ say we need a little
time to think about it ♪
♪ because we're men ♪
♪ we're gonna pay more for the movies,
chop down trees,
and eat a lot of meat ♪
♪ because we're men ♪
♪ and we can have our own
kids, but we're gonna wait until
we meet the right person because
it's an important decision ♪
♪ but in the meantime, we can barbecue ♪
♪ buy power tools ♪
♪ get tattoos ♪
♪ buy our own sho-o-o-o-es ♪
wait. No, we can't.
We don't have any money.
Let's get jobs! Well, as far as i can see
from your... Résumé, you have
absolutely no qualifications whatsoever.
Do either of you have
any applicable skills?
Well, i can do this.
Look, for the third time,
Mr. watterson, rolling your
stomach is not a valuable
skill in the work environment.
I-I'm sorry. Point taken. Good.
Okay, so, looking at your track re...
I see. Sorry. Look, right now, i need you
to give me a valid reason why i
should even consider
giving either of you a job.
Well, i can touch my nose with my tongue.
That's not a skill. This is.
You guys want a job?
Well, you can have mine!
I quit! Good luck!
Yay! What do people with jobs do?
I don't know. Hiring and firing? Cool!
Well, you're hired. So are you! What now?
Guess we should do some firing?
You're fired!
You're fired! You're fired! You're fired!
And you're fired!
Hey, what are you firing me for?
It's what i do. Well, you're fired!
You can't fire me!
I just fired you!
All right, quickly, hire me again.
Okay. You're hired.
You're fired! I can't believe
we lost our jobs. So, this is being an
adult? No money. No job.
Crumbly apartment.
Rent overdue! And this is our last
piece of food.
I think we should share it.
Sorry. What was that? I can't believe you
ate our last piece of candy!
Well, i can't
believe I'm stuck here with you!
I can't believe we're
both yelling! I know!
We're trying to hide from the
landlord! Let's be quiet, then!
Okay! I wish we were kids again. Me too.
I'll be in my room. Me too.
Someone's coming! No!
It's the landlord! What are we gonna do?
I don't know! Unh! Uhhhh! Uhhhhhh!
Aaaaah! Please don't hurt us!
Take anything you want!
Guys, it's me... your sister.
Dude, you look like
a Mexican wrestler.
I'm not a man, and neither are you.
I think i know what happened. Follow me.
Come on. Stay up. Stay up!
Yes! No! Now, come on!
Flex! Flex, flex! Richard?
What are you doing?
I'm getting old.
It's like you always say...
"we grow up so fat."
"Fast," Richard, and i
was talking about the children.
Don't talk to me
about those rosy-cheeked, baby-faced...
Hairy mutants!
Hi. What's happened to my babies?
It's okay, mom.
I think it was these
that turned us into men.
You found my supplements.
But they're empty.
Can someone please tell
me what's going on? Sure.
At breakfast, dad left with
the cereal box, so we ate his
supplements by mistake.
I think i know what happened.
Yeah, i just told you.
Richard, why on earth
were you buying those supplements?
I couldn't help myself.
It's the Internet's fault.
Every time i open my e-mails,
this is what i get. Are you too fat? Yes.
Are you too bald? Maybe.
Are you really the man she
deserves? No!
So, that's where all the laptops went.
It was a moment of weakness,
and i crumbled, Nicole!
I crumbled!
Honey, you didn't need those pills.
I love you just the way you are.
So do we, dad. Really?
Come here, my little... Body builders.
So, are we gonna be like this forever?
It says on the box
that the effect wears off after a week.
At least that pyramid
scheme will be more reliable.
Anyway, now this is all cleared up,
let's all get out
the house and have some fun.
Higher! Higher!
They grow up so fast. Precious mo...