[ Upbeat music plays ]
Am i invited?
Gumball: Am i invited?
Darwin: Am i invited?
Guys! Guys!
Let me cut to the chase here,
all right?
You're all invited.
All: Yay!
A high-school party, and we're
all invited!
None of you are invited!!
Oh, hi, Rachel.
My party is for young adults,
not old babies!
Tch, tch, tch.
Rachel, Rachel, Rachel.
Wouldn't it be a shame if mom
and dad found out about your
secret party?
All: Tch, tch, tch.
Rachel, Rachel, Rachel.
Fine. You can come.
But you all have to bring...
A date!
All: A date?
Uh-huh.
Good luck.
All: Aaaaaaaaaah!
Darwin: What's a date?
Hey! What's a date?
Hmm.
A secret house party, eh?
I'd better tell principal brown.
Gumball: All right, buddy,
let's make a list of possible
dates.
Darwin: What's a date?
Date. D-a-t-e.
Social activity undertaken by
two people to assess their
suitability for a relationship.
[ Whir ]
It is also a fruit that makes
you poop.
Gumball: Yeah...
Thanks?
Darwin: Hey, what about
penny?
Gumball: Uh, penny?
Oh, no, no, no.
I just like her as a friend.
Darwin: Why are your eyes
shaped like hearts?
Gumball: Allergies.
Darwin: Oh.
Well, what about Carrie?
Gumball: Carrie.
She's got spirit.
[ Plunk! ]
I'll put her in the "maybes."
Next.
Teri.
Nicely drawn features but a
little flat.
I'll put her in the "possiblys."
Hmmm.
Carmen -- prickly but smart.
Interesting.
Um...
Saucy.
[ Chomping ]
Gumball: No.
[ Plop! ]
Darwin: What's that?
Gumball: "Would you be the
jelly in my peanut butter
sandwich?"
Hmm.
[ Pop! Pop! Pop! Pop! Pop! ]
What do you say, gumball?
Gumball: Eh, no, thanks.
I already ate.
All right, buddy, it's date
time!
Hey, masami!
Want to be my date?
You're not really my type 'cause
i usually like attractive girls,
but, hey, beggars can't be
choosers!
[ Rumble! ]
You are a girl, right?
What?
[ Zap! ]
[ Coughing ]
How about you, Teri?
You look desperate.
[ Gasps ]
[ Riffle! ]
Gumball: Was that a slap?
Yes.
Gumball: Uh...Ouch?
Oh!
Hey, saucy, it's your lucky day.
You're my date for the party.
What do you say?
Phew.
Gumball: [ Gasps deeply ]
[ Laughs ]
Date fail!
Come on, prickles, let's roll!
Gumball: Ohhhh!
Dad: Oh, cheer up, gumball.
When i was your age, i needed a
date for a party, and what i
said to her was...
[ Mumbling ]
And 20 years later, we're still
married.
Gumball: Oh, dad, you make it
sound so easy.
Anais: Are you sure you've
asked every girl in class?
Darwin: You didn't ask penny.
Gumball: Penny?
She's too hot.
Not -- not hot.
Nhot...My type.
Not my type.
[ Laughs nervously ]
Anais: Well, if it's not
penny, there's still one girl
you haven't asked.
Gumball: Really? Who?
Oh -- her.
[ Rattle! ]
[ Ringing ]
[ Beep ]
Hi, this is gumball watterson
calling.
Will you be my date for the
party?
Uh, no, you weren't exactly the
first girl i asked, but...
No! No, no, no! don't hang up!
Please, i can beg.
Yes, I'm on my knees.
Hey, I'm not saying that!
No! No, no, no!
Please, don't hang up!
[ Sighs ]
Fine.
I, gumball watterson, have a
stupid face stuck on a big,
stupid head with a tiny, stupid
brain, and stupid is my favorite
color.
[ All chuckle ]
[ Gasps ] You will?!
Oh, thank you, thank you, thank
you so much!
I'll pick you up at 8:00.
[ Beep ]
Darwin: Oof!
Gumball: Yes!
See, Darwin?
No girl can resist me.
Dad: I'm so proud of you.
My baby boy's becoming a man!
Gumball: Uh, yeah.
Keep it together, dad.
Dad: It seems like only
yesterday we were watching
"Daisy the donkey" together.
Gumball: Dad, that was
yesterday.
Dad: Well, it feels like a
long time ago.
And look at you now!
Dating a girl!
[ Doorbell rings ]
[ Thump! Thump! Thump! ]
Hey.
Darwin: Hello.
Gumball: Hi, penny.
Yeah. Hi, gumball.
Gumball: So...Uh, i didn't
realize you were coming with
Hector.
I didn't realize you like
lizard breath.
[ Growls ]
[ Sniffs ]
[ Groans ]
Darwin: I feel awkward.
Ah. More guests have arrived.
Shall we make our move?
Patience, Nigel.
Let's wait until it's in full
swing.
[ Gasps ]
Ugh.
Tobias!
More of your dweeb, loser, baby
friends have arrived.
[ Panting ]
[ Screech! ]
Guys! Guys!
This party is totally off the
hook!
[ Mid-tempo music plays ]
[ Singing ]
Anyone for more tea?
don't mind if i do.
Whoo-hoo!
This is such fun!
[ Chomping ]
Gumball: This is a
high-school party?
Darwin: I know.
It's awesome!
Whooooooooo!
Want to dance?
Gumball: Uh, you go ahead.
I'll join you later.
Whoo!
Darwin: [ Laughs ]
I'm having the time of my
life!
[ Doorbell rings ]
[ Crash! ]
[ All gasp ]
This party is busted!
Busted wide open!
Busted.
Now for some real music!
[ Click ]
[ Dance music plays ]
Aaaah!
Rock on!
[ All cheering ]
Hey, look!
I'm gonna throw the TV out of
the window!
Please -- allow me.
[ Glass shatters ]
No! Not the TV!
Yaaaaah!
[ Whooping ]
That's my girl!
Whoo-hoo!
Hey, dude, I'm trying to
sleep here!
Sorry.
[ Sobbing ]
Darwin: Hello!
Hey, why are you crying?
Because this is the worst
party ever!
I invited everybody, and none of
my friends turned out!
Darwin: Well, we all came,
and we're your friends.
You guys aren't my friends.
You just trashed my parents'
house!
[ Glass shatters ]
[ Laughs ]
Darwin: don't worry.
I'll tidy it up.
Yeah, sure.
You're gonna tidy all this up?
Darwin: Of course!
don't you know I'm part sucker
fish?
[ Whoop! Whoop! Whoop! Whoop! ]
Thanks.
[ Sniffles ]
What's your name?
Darwin: Darwin raglan caspian
ahab Poseidon nicodemus
watterson III.
[ Giggles ]
You don't seem so bad for a kid.
[ Slow music plays ]
[ Snoring ]
[ Chomping ]
[ Laughs ]
I'm doing the mashed potato!
[ Gasps ]
Thirsty!
Hey.
How's your date?
Gumball: Great.
How's yours?
Hector's not really my type.
Gumball, do you remember that
paper plane?
Gumball: Um...
Oh, yeah.
"Will you be the jelly in my
peanut butter sandwich"?
I wasn't really hungry.
[ Laughs ]
No, silly.
I was the peanut butter.
Gumball: What?!
Oh.
I was supposed to be the jelly,
wasn't i?
You seriously didn't
understand?
Gumball: Uh...No.
Hey, Tina, can i have the
next dance?
You can have this one.
Gumball: [ Gasps ]
[ Guuuuuuuust! ]
[ Plunk! ]
[ Ptoo! ]
[ Ting! ]
Darwin: Finished!
Darwin!
You're the best kid ever!
How come you don't have a
girlfriend?
Darwin: What do i need a
girlfriend for?
This.
Mwah!
[ Honk! ]
Darwin: Everything is so
clear now.
[ Thud! ]
Is he gonna be all right?
Gumball: Yeah, yeah, he'll be
fine.
Uh, penny?
Yes?
Gumball: Um...I was thinking
about the, you know, next party.
Maybe you could be the sandwich
in my, uh,
peanut-jelly-butter...
You know what i mean.
Yeah. I'd love to.
[ Car horn blaring ]
[ Horn honks ]
I think your dad's here.
Gumball: Oh, well.
Time to go.
I guess.
Come on, buddy.
Thanks for the party!
I love you, penny!
What did i say that for?!
Is that really the best we
can do?
I think he's awesome.
[ Car door closes ]
Dad: I like the new one
better.
Gumball: Who? What? Penny?
Oh, no, i-i don't love her.
I-i mean, love her.
I-i mean, like her.
Can we go home, please?
Dad: And how was the party
for you, Darwin?
Darwin: I don't know how to
exactly put it into words,
but...
[ Inhales ]
[ Yodeling ]
[ Trilling ]
[ Door opens, closes ]
See?
Didn't i tell you we could trust
Rachel and Tobias while we were
away?
Heh.
Wait till we see the phone bill.
[ Door creaks ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Birds chirping ]
Gumball: Look, Darwin.
We waited more than seven months
for this.
Darwin: I know!
We waited so long, i had time to
grow hair.
Gumball: Huh?
Whoa.
May i touch it?
Darwin: You may.
Gumball: Nice.
Darwin: Thanks.
Come on! Put the game on!
Gumball: Come on, come on.
[ Gasps ]
Oh, there you are.
There's something wrong with it!
Darwin: Try the other way
around!
Gumball: [ Grunting ]
Darwin: Come on!
Can't you see I'm practically
flipping my flippers?
Gumball: What is that
supposed to mean?
Darwin: It means put the game
on!
Gumball: I can't!
It's not working!
I think we got stiffed.
I'm sorry, kids, but it's
store policy.
I can't give you a refund.
Gumball: What? You have to!
We asked you a ton of questions
before we bought it, remember?
What's bigger -- a lion or a
tiger?
A tiger.
Gumball: Why is the sky blue?
Diffraction of light through
nitrogen.
Darwin: Can anything escape
from a black hole?
Not unless it's a superheated
quasar.
Gumball: What is 2,352 times
1,035?
2,434,320.
Gumball: If you know all this
stuff, how come you're a store
clerk?
Look, you want this game or
not?
Gumball: We'll take it.
Actually, you never asked me
anything about the game.
Gumball: Oh. You're right.
But whatever!
You have to give us a refund!
It's been less than 24 hours!
Look, guys, if it was up to
me, I'd totally give you a
refund, but the manager won't
allow it.
[ Whir ]
[ Laughs nervously ]
I-I'm sorry, but that's the
way it is.
Thanks for shopping at
Ripley 2000.
Gumball: This is not the end
of it, Larry needlemeyer!
Mark my words!
We will get a refund!
Hi, Larry.
Can we have a refund, please?
Get out of here!
Gumball: Ripley 2000.
More like "rip-off" 2000!
Darwin: Why is it 2000,
anyway?
It's not like it's the future
anymore!
[ Telephone buzzes ]
Hi.
Yes, Mr. manager.
Uh, no, sir, i certainly didn't
give a refund to those kids.
Yes, i brought your suit to the
dry cleaners and walked your
dogs.
Actually, the big one bit me.
Oh, yes, he can be playful.
This is why i was seven minutes
late.
Oh, yes, Mr. manager, sir, it
was entirely my fault.
It won't happen again, sir.
Have a nice --
[ Click, dial tone ]
Gumball: [ Amplified ] This
is the police!
You're surrounded!
Put your hands where i can see
them!
Now put your hands on the cash
register and take out $20!
[ Cash register dings ]
Now come outside and swap it for
this computer game!
Hey!
What kind of police are you?
Gumball: The...Super-real
police.
The...Refund department...Of
justice!
Nice try, kids.
Gumball: Darn!
Oh, look, kids, I'm not gonna
give you a refund.
Gumball: We're not here to
ask for a refund.
We just want you to look at my
new, shiny watch.
I, uh, it's kind of hard when
you...Swing...It...Like...That.
Darwin: Did it work?
Is he hypnotized?
Gumball: Let's test it.
Okay.
You're the world's most amazing
dancer.
[ Ding! ]
[ Classical music plays ]
[ Both laugh ]
Gumball: Okay, now...
Now you're an ostrich.
Darwin: No, a gorilla!
Gumball: A gorilla ostrich!
[ Ding! ]
[ Chittering, squawking ]
[ Both laugh ]
Darwin: And have roller
skates on!
Gumball: And your butt's on
fire!
[ Both laugh ]
[ Crash! ]
[ Groaning ]
Gumball: And now you're a
store clerk giving us a refund?
Sorry.
It's against store policy.
Gumball: [ Sighs ]
Now your butt's on fire again.
Aaaaaaaaah!
[ Door opens ]
Oh, come on.
I told you -- no refund.
Gumball: Oh, no, no, no, no,
no.
We're not going to ask you for a
refund.
We just want two minutes of your
time.
[ Click ]
Every year, hundreds of
children buy faulty computer
games and don't get refunds.
This is Jimmy.
[ Whap! ]
Jimmy really needed a refund,
but the store manager wouldn't
give it to him.
Darwin: I don't care that
you're sad, Jimmy.
It's store policy!
Gumball: Jimmy's life is now
very bad, and he lives in a
shoe box.
What's that, Jimmy?
Yes, yes, Jimmy.
I know you're sad and lonely.
[ Mid-tempo music plays ]
Darwin: ¶ refund the world ¶
¶ refund it sooner ¶
gumball: ¶ uphold the rights
that little Jimmy had as a
consumer ¶
Darwin: ¶ now he's living in
a box ¶
gumball: ¶ he's a victim of
deceit ¶
both: ¶ and even though he
still had the receipt ¶
[ voice breaking ] Poor
Jimmy.
I-i had no idea it was such a
big problem.
[ Sobs ]
Is there anything i can do?
Gumball: Well, you could look
into your heart and...
Both: Give us a refund?
I'm sorry, but no.
Gumball: Well, you leave us
no choice, Larry.
I'm gonna slap myself, and
Darwin's gonna hold his breath
until you do something!
Darwin: [ Inhales ]
Gumball: Aah! Aah!
This is on you, Larry!
Oh!
You can just stop all this
suffering with just one word!
Aah! Oh!
Okay, okay!
Please stop.
Look, maybe i could --
[ Whir ]
[ Chuckles nervously ]
I'm sorry, but "no" means "no."
Gumball: [ Groans ]
Dad: Hey, kids! What's up?
Gumball: We couldn't get a
refund, and now we're really
cheesed off.
Dad: Watch your language,
young man!
"Cheese" is not to be invoked in
vain in this house!
But if it's a refund you're
after, you've come to the right
place -- person -- man --
rabbit.
Gumball: Really?
Let's go there right now!
Dad: Wait.
If you're going to do something,
you got to do it right.
Heh!
[ George thorogood & the
destroyers' "bad to the bone"
plays ]
[ Grunting ]
Now how do i look?
Gumball: Actually, you look
like your wedding picture.
Dad: Perfect.
Now, hand me that game.
[ "Bad to the bone" continues ]
[ Breathing shakily ]
What do you want from me, you
nut burger?!
Dad: Oh, you know what we
want.
Gumball: We want what's
rightfully ours, and we brought
our dad!
Dad: Exactly.
For the last time, i can't!
Dad: Uhp!
I wish to speak to your manager.
But you don't realize -- he's
a vile, cruel beast!
[ Whir ]
Uh, sorry. No refund.
Dad: Shhh.
Tch, tch, tch.
Okay.
Here's what's gonna happen.
I'm gonna return this game and
get a refund.
Look.
I'm putting the game on the
counter.
B-but --
dad: Easy.
Easy, pal.
Now, I'm opening the register.
No, no, no!
Sir, sir, sir, i wouldn't do
that if i were you!
Dad: Well, lucky for me, I'm
not you.
So now I'm going to take what
you owe us.
See my hand?
Slowly, slowly.
Gumball: Wait.
Isn't that, like, stealing?
But you don't understand!
You can't take money out of the
register!
You can only put it in!
[ Creak! ]
[ Alarm blaring ]
Nooooooo!
We're doomed!
Dad: Aah!
What's going on?!
He's coming!
Dad: Who's coming?!
The manager!
Dad: Aaaah!
I'm putting it back!
[ Sobbing ] I'm putting it back!
[ Gasps ]
Aaaaaah!
[ Wailing ]
Please! don't hurt me!
It's not even my fault!
It's their fault!
Gumball: What?!
When you said you'd get us a
refund, we didn't expect you to
steal from the register!
Dad: You know very well i
can't be trusted!
Aaaaah!
[ Whimpers ]
[ Blaring stops ]
[ Laughs ]
Look at you!
I thought you were going to be
some huge dude!
[ Laughs ]
The look on our faces!
Whoa!
I mean, where's the light in
your office?
It must be on the floor in the
back of the room or something!
[ Laughs ]
Phew!
So, can we have our refund now?
No refund!
Dad: Oh, come on.
We've all had a laugh and a
little fright, but i think it's
time to just give us our money
back, and we'll be on our way.
I've had it with you and your
brats trying to mess with my
money!
You think you can steal from me
and laugh in my face?
Dad: [ Laughs ]
Oh, you're adorable!
But, seriously, though, you
don't want this to get physical.
You're lucky I'm a pacifist.
[ Growls ]
Aah!
Dad: Ow.
Ow!
Get him off! Get him off!
Get him off!
Gumball: Go, dad!
Whoo-hoo!
Come on, dad!
You got him!
Dad: Think he's on my back!
Aaaah!
Darwin: Yeah, kick his butt,
dad!
Gumball: Come on, dad!
You can take him!
Dad?
Dad: Get him off!
Get him off!
Aah! Ow!
Darwin: He's not winning, is
he?
Gumball: No.
Dad: What's wrong with you?
Ow! Ow!
Doesn't really hurt that much.
But ow!
Oh, no!
My beautiful face!
Gumball! Darwin!
Stop this!
Gumball: Eh, this is getting
kind of embarrassing.
Dad: No!
don't abandon me, please!
Ow!
Aah!
He's biting my neck with his
little teeth, and it tickles!
[ Laughs ]
[ Sobbing ]
Gumball: Stop right there,
little man!
Darwin: Yeah!
Leave Mr. dad alone!
Otherwise --
otherwise what?
Gumball: Otherwise, we'll put
the security video online.
What do you think the Internet
will say when it sees you
slapping your customers with
your little hands?
That it's pretty funny?
Gumball: Yeah, it was pretty
funny.
But you'll probably get a modest
fine and a couple of days of
community service.
So?
Gumball: So the shop will be
closed.
And?
Gumball: And you'll lose
money.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
No need to get excited.
Okay, look, i can't give you a
refund.
It's a matter of principle.
But since i find you quite
pathetic, I'll give you a 1%
discount on this new game
console.
That way, you can play the game
you've already got.
What do you say?
Gumball: Hmm.
1%.
So, $700.
That's, like, $7 off!
Dad: Now, that's what i call
a bargain!
Darwin: Can we have your
credit card, Mr. dad?
Dad: Totally.
All: Whoo-hoo!
Dad: Ugh!
Can't believe i got beat up by a
garden gnome.
Gumball: Oh, come on.
It was pretty funny.
Darwin: Like when you were
screaming, "no, no, my beautiful
face!"
Gumball: And when he was
pounding on you from above and
it looked like a tennis ball
bouncing on a melon.
[ Laughter ]
Dad: And thanks to me, we did
get a huge discount on the
console.
Darwin: Come on!
Put the game on!
Gumball: Yes!
[ Buzzing ]
Dad, he sold us a shredder.
Dad: [ Sighs ]
[ Grunting ]
[ "Bad to the bone" plays ]