[upbeat music playing]
[Tobias] You want it, come get it.
Hey, give it back! Put it down!
-Daisy! Leave her alone!
-I got it.
Come on, Tobias, over here!
Gumball, do something!
Sorry, there's nothing I can do, sis.
You broke childhood rule number four--
Never get a toy out on a school bus.
You were the one who brought her on board!
Huh. Well, let that be
a lesson to all of us.
Oh, Gumball, please get Daisy back for me.
That's what big brothers
are supposed to do.
Hmm. I don't know.
I'm not much of a fighter.
I'm more of a... Uh...
-A coward?
-That's the word.
[Anais sniffles]
-[sighs] OK. Let me see what I can do.
-Give it here,
-come on!
-Who wants it next?
Hey, punk, give me that donkey or else.
[chuckles] Or what?
Whoa.
You do not want to know.
Really? What if I do this?
Then you would unleash the full fury
of my terrifying anger.
Mountains will shake! Cities will crumble!
The skies will be ripped apart,
and the meteor of my wrath will
grind you to dust!
Oops.
Oh, man.
Kind of hoped you'd buy the bluff.
Daisy!
No!
No, no!
Relax, sis. It's only a toy.
[growling] No, it's not.
OK, we'll get it back.
-[Anais] Daisy!
-Oh.
[school bell ringing]
Seriously, dude, you got to give it back.
My sister is blowing a fuse.
Sorry, guys. I gave it to Juke.
[beatboxing]
Nice beats, but not much help.
[beatboxing, laughing]
[Gumball and Darwin] Daisy!
-Yay!
-Whoo-hoo!
[thud]
[clears throat]
Hector, I think
you're sitting on something.
Uh... OK, this is a little embarrassing.
-You tell him.
-Excuse me, sir.
You appear to have a little something
stuck to your right buttock.
Huh?
I got it!
What is wrong with me?
I got it, I got it, I got it!
I don't got it.
[groans]
Why?
Sweet dreams! [braying]
-Excuse me, milady, but it seems--
-[roars]
-Plan B?
-Yeah.
[sniffles, sighs]
Anais, Anais!
-Look what we found.
-[gasps]
Daisy!
Wait a minute.
That's not the real one.
No, it's much better.
Look.
[singing]
Hmm. Weak attempt to pawn me off
with a cheap replacement.
Where's my Daisy?
Sweaty hands...
nervous body language.
You know who's got her, don't you?
-No.
Your eyes just darted to the left.
You're lying, aren't you?
[both] No.
It's Tina, isn't it?
-No--
-No.
Yeah, it's Tina.
Listen, Gumball, I am not spending
the night without Daisy.
You'll just have to go to Tina's place
and get her back.
What? Why me?
Because-- because--
Because you were the one
who lost it in the first place.
But I'm just a little boy,
and she's a giant T-Rex.
But you are my big brother.
But I don't want
to get my face pounded to a pulp.
Ugh. Fine. I'll go.
But you two are coming with me.
Oh.
Man, this place is scary.
Is that really her bedroom?
-It's a dump.
-Literally.
-It's really sad.
-[Tina snoring]
[gasps] Look.
-Daisy!
-[continues snoring]
OK, here's the plan--
Get inside, lift up her arm, take the toy,
and get out of there.
You got that, Darwin? Go.
I'm not doing that!
I'm not either.
There's a T-Rex in there.
Well, one of you better go.
-Otherwise, I'm telling Mom.
-Hmm.
Getting told off by Mom
or fighting a T-Rex...
Mom, T-Rex, Mom, T-Rex...
Well, I'm going with the T-Rex.
Yeah. No contest.
[snoring continues]
[Darwin making funny noise]
Darwin, why are you making that noise?
I'm sorry!
I always do it when I'm nervous.
Well, stop it!
[muffled noises continue]
[roars]
I'm not getting any closer to that thing.
Wait here.
-Anais!
-What?
You see that pole over there?
-Throw it to me.
-OK.
No, no.
He can't catch.
Here it comes.
-Ow.
-[loud clang]
[growls]
[snores]
-[whispering] I'm OK.
-Shh.
Careful. Careful!
I'm sorry! It's just really hard
to maneuver a long pole.
Look. It's like she's smiling.
Happy, sad, happy, sad.
Hey, Darwin, look.
[toots]
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.
-What are you doing?
-Don't worry. She'll never wake up.
[squeaking]
[snoring]
OK, I think we have to move her.
[both grunting]
Hold it, buddy!
Let me see.
-Gumball!
-Shh! What?
You have to help me.
Yeah, yeah, just two seconds.
-Help... Aah!
-[bones cracking]
[gasps]
[continues snoring]
[grunting, panting]
I'm OK.
[both sigh]
[gasps] Yes, yes!
I got it!
Sweet dreams... [braying]
Run!
[screaming]
[roars]
[panting]
-Gumball!
-What?
[screaming]
-[roars]
-[screams]
[sighs]
-I think we're safe now.
-[all scream]
Run!
-[roars]
-[panting]
Where's Darwin?
This was a stupid idea!
I know! Should we just give it to her?
No! She's mine!
OK. You have it, then.
Gumball, help me!
I can't! I'm too much of a coward!
Uh... Fine.
Throw me Daisy!
It's what she's after.
OK. Go long.
Uh, Gumball, she's after us now!
Don't worry. You know I can't catch.
I hate myself.
I hate yourself.
[screams]
Psst. Over here!
[growling]
[gasps] The gate!
We're nearly there. It's almost over.
Not so fast.
[both scream]
Darwin, keep absolutely still.
Her vision is based on movement.
That only works in movies.
Yay!
Daisy!
You know, Tina,
there's a lesson in this somewhere.
Don't mess with the Wattersons.
[singing]
♪ You know ♪
Who's the boss now?
I'm sorry.
It's just that I never had a toy before.
I swear, I...
I wanted to give it back,
but... but she helped me to sleep.
[sniffles]
It's just so scary here.
Man! Those puppy eyes again.
I feel really bad now.
You know what, Tina?
I think you need Daisy more than I do.
-Really?
-Yeah.
She'll look after you when you're scared.
Besides, I don't need her anymore.
I've got Darwin and Gumball
to look after me.
-Group hug.
That's very touching.
But now you'd better start running.
[all] Why?
My dad eats trespassers.
-[thud]
-[roars]
OK, kids.
Mom will be home any minute now.
Have you all wrapped
your birthday presents?
[all] Yay!
And you, Dad-- What did you get her?
Nothing!
[all] What?
[screams]
I forgot! What am I gonna do?
What am I gonna do? What am I gonna do?
[whimpering]
How about you buy her a present?
Yes! Wait! No. I have to watch the kids.
Hmm.
Hey, guys,
you don't have to watch the kids.
Here's a $20.
Go buy her something special
from the gas station.
-[Gumball and Darwin] Yay! Adventure!
-[door opens, closes]
Welcome to the gas station,
where we never sleep,
'cause we're not allowed to.
[both] Hi, mister.
Can I help you?
Yeah. Can it and hand over the cash.
[chuckles] Uh...
-What?
-Don't make me use this.
Oh, my gosh. He's got a spoon!
He's got a spoon!
Sucker.
Show it again! Show it again!
OK, but it's the last time.
We have to get it back home.
It's like the best gift ever!
Yeah.
Mom's gonna love it.
Excuse me, sir, what are you doing?
[gasps] Are you robbing the store?
Nah. I'm collecting for charity.
-[both] Whoa.
-Awesomely kind. Which charity is it?
Huh? Oh, eh, eh...
Bald people.
Can we help?
You're kidding, right?
We'd never joke about bald people.
Ha! All right, kids.
Just go fill up the baggie
with anything valuable.
[both] Yay!
Heh. Suckers.
What could bring a smile to their little,
bald faces?
Hmm.
Oh, oh. Sunglasses!
[both] Ooh!
Bikinis!
[both] Whoa!
Fake mustache!
Makeup!
Wigs?
Nah.
-[Gumball] A princess tiara?
-[Darwin] Yeah!
[both] I'm bald and I'm proud.
Uh-oh.
Five-o. Here come the po-po.
Hey, Mr. Charity Man, we're done!
Hey, I need you
to do something for me.
[both] Yay! More charity work!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
You see that man?
It'll spoil the surprise
if he sees me here.
I'm pretty famous in the charity business.
[both] Oh!
-I get it.
-So you distract him for me.
-[both] Yay!
-Haha!
That's the third burrito I've had,
and I'm still hungry.
Hi, officer.
How can we distract you today?
I'm sort of looking
for something that could fill me up.
[both] Follow us.
How about a hot dog? They're delicious.
Nah!
-No.
-There's a mustache on your sausage.
Yeah. It's our secret ingredient.
I think I'll go for something
without hair.
-Maybe some marshmallow heart stoppers.
-[gasps]
Nah, not enough sugar.
Oh.
A doughnut.
That could fill a hole.
Just get rid of him.
[both] OK.
-You want it?
-Yes, yes, yes!
-Really?
-Yes!
-You really, really want it?
Then... fetch.
[pants]
He's gone, Mr. Charity Man.
Great. Good job.
Now get back to looting--
I mean, collecting for charity.
[both] Yay!
Now, let's get back to business.
[screams]
So, Mr. Employee of the Month,
where is the safe?
I won't tell you anything.
They would fire me.
Oh, really?
What would they do about this?
No, please!
They'll take it off my salary.
Whoops.
You heartless monster. That was 25 cents.
Now, where is the safe?
-I won't tell you.
-[glass shatters]
-Oops.
-No! That was 35 cents.
-Wait! That was $2.50, reduced from $3.95.
-Now will you talk?
-Never!
-Your choice.
-No!
Look, Darwin. Shampoo.
Perfect for bald people.
-Ooh.
-What's that?
It's a safe, Darwin. It's full of money.
And what do bald people need more of?
-Friends?
-Exactly.
-And how do you buy friends?
-Uh...
With money.
[both] Yay!
Huh. There's a lock.
What number should I try?
-Um, two!
-[beeps]
-Doesn't work.
-Seven!
[beeps]
-No.
-Nine!
-Nope.
-Well, that's all the numbers I know.
-Try two again. [sighs]
-[beeps]
I guess we'll have to use brute force.
-Happy Birthday!
[gasps] Oh.
Thanks.
Where are the boys?
Well, I forgot your birthday,
so I sent them down to
the gas station to get you a present.
What?
Oh.
Is it the birthday or sending two kids
downtown at night on their own?
Put your pants on and get in the car!
[panting]
We're never gonna crack it.
You know, you only have to ask nicely.
[both] Please.
[both] Whoa!
Can't believe you sent the kids
to the gas station at this hour.
Come on, honey.
What's the worst that could happen?
-Hey.
-Freeze, suckers!
He's got a spoon! [screaming]
Ha! Sucker.
Hey, Mr. Charity Man,
we found money for the...
bald.
Hi, Mom. Hi, Dad. Why are you tied up?
Oh.
He's not really a good guy, is he?
Oh, come on!
-Now give me the money!
-No!
Run, Darwin, run!
Give me that bag right now!
Give me the money!
Oh, come on.
You're not gonna stop me
with a marshmallow.
Ow. That sausage was frozen!
[Gumball grunts]
Grr.
[muffled speech]
[sighs]
Don't worry. I've covered his approach
with maple syrup.
And I've covered our way out.
What?
How am I supposed to escape?
Watch out! He's coming.
[panting]
[both grunt]
Gotcha!
[grunts]
[muffled speech]
Ice cream!
Give me that money...
Or I'll tear it out of
your sorry little hands.
Come on.
You know I'll find ya.
Where are ya?
[hissing]
What the--
Try and catch us now!
[panting]
-Aah.
-Faster!
He's gaining on us! We need to go faster!
OK!
Is that fast enough?
Yes!
[screaming]
Yes! We made it! [laughing]
Oh.
[gasps]
Game over, suckers.
Not yet.
No!
Ha-ha. Now give me the dough.
[both] No!
-Gimme!
-No!
All right. You've asked for this.
Oh, my gosh! He's got a spoon!
Such violence.
[laughing]
You suckers.
[thud]
Oh, my poor little angels,
are you all right?
Hey, guys, I just realized
I didn't pay for the doughn...
Drop the sausage, lady!
Oh, come on. It wasn't me.
It was the fingerprint... guy.
Tell that to the judge, lady.
[all] Happy Birthday, Mom!
[all] You're the coolest Mom ever.
[all] We love you, Mom.
OK, lady, you're in the clear.
We caught this guy trying to rob
a convenience store with a spoon!
A spoon! [laughs]
Sucker. All right, lady.
Give me five minutes to do the paperwork
and you'll be out of here.
[all] Yay!
Five minutes is all I need.
[upbeat music playing]