Aah! It's Daisy the donkey on ice day!
You promised to take me, and
we're late!
Honey, I'm sorry.
Mommy worked really late last
night.
What sort of a horrible mother
wouldn't take her daughter to
her favorite show?
Anais, i know what i said,
but... Horrible mother...
Horrible mother...
Okay. "Electrofat.
Gets you fit while you watch
TV."
So the last electrode goes...
♪ Daisy the donkey ♪ Where? ♪ Daisy ♪
There! Hi, honey!
Hi. Where's gumball and Darwin?
In the backyard playing
their made-up game.
Keep an eye on them.
Every time they play that game,
it's a mess.
♪ Daisy ♪
Dodge or dare! Relax, honey. I'm here.
What could go wrong?
Dodge or dare!
Dodge or dare! Yes. What could go wrong?
Daisy the donkey! Ooh!
Now come on, electrofat.
Make me beautiful!
Aah! Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
What was that?
Doesn't matter.
It's time to play...
Dodge or dare!
Roll the dice!
Take a card!
Dare!
You have to throw the ball onto
the moon using only objects from
the trash. Hah.
Just watch and learn. Yes!
Ooh. Aah! Hey, the card says
"no hands." Mmmmm.
I told you, Margaret.
It's not a mid-life crisis.
It's just a new car.
It landed in the Robinson's yard. Yay!
Mr. Robinson. He's such a funny guy.
Mrs. Robinson is one lucky lady.
Your ball fell into my
garden, causing my wife's hair
to fall off!
Therefore, as a punishment, I'll
teach you a new game called,
um...
Learning the consequences of
your actions!
A game Mr. Robinson
invented for us?
You can start by cleaning the
garden.
Yes!
But wait!
There you go.
You wouldn't want it to be easy,
would you?
Whoo!
We'll see if they're still
smiling after this.
Excuse me. There, we're done.
This is green, green-orange,
orangey green, terra-cotta,
Egyptian sunrise, sunset yellow,
and this is the Mr. Robinson
head-shaped leaf.
Ooh.
Can we keep it?
No.
You slackers forgot to cut the
grass! Mr. Robinson, you're so right.
What... Were... We...
Thinking?!
We'll get right on
it.
But wait!
You got to use nail clippers.
Yay!
Thank you, Mr. Robinson.
I think they're missing the
- point.
- Done!
What the...?! >> Whoa!
All right, goons.
Come here and paint this fence
blue.
Yay!
That'll teach 'em to mess
with gaylord Robinson.
Done! >> Hmph! Now make it green! Done!
Orange with purple stripes!
Done!
Yellow with black dots!
Done! >> Pink! Done!
Red! Done! >> Blue!
Done! >> Black! Done!
Yellow! Done! >> Aaaaaah!
Mr. Robinson, since
you love painting so much, i
made this bird especially for
you. >> thanks?
Ooh, yeah.
Follow me.
Now, there's a stain on this
rug. Where?
There!
I mean, there!
What?! More ice, sir? >> give me that!
What?! Okay, now you're scaring me.
I'm sure Mr.
Robinson needs more help.
Maybe he's too shy to
ask. >> Go away! He hides it well,
but i can feel he needs us. >> Go away!
Go away! Go awaaaaaay!
Now that is a cry for help.
Those little parasites, they
just won't...
Hi, Mr. Robinson. >> What?!
Don't touch me! Unbelievable.
Come on. Eat up, Mr. Robinson.
Get away from me! Darn those kids.
Can't a guy get some privacy in
his own house?
Blast it. Out of paper. Get out of here!
Wait. Could you throw that back,
please? I need to lie down.
It's bedtime, Mr. Robinson.
I think he has a temperature. Come on,
Mr. Robinson.
Say ""
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Listen, kids.
Why are you trying so hard to
help me?
Because we love you,
Mr. Robinson.
But there's nothing left for
you to do!
We could clean your new
car. No way! My car is brand-new and very
expensive. We could clean Mrs. Robinson?
All right. Clean the car.
Yay!
But, but, but, but please be
careful with it!
So... Where do we start? I don't know.
I never cleaned a car before.
It doesn't matter.
Let's make Mr. Robinson proud.
Okay. Easy. Mr. Robinson said it's very
expensive. I know. I'll just...
At least things can't get any
worse. Aaaaaah!
You know, Margaret, maybe
those kids aren't so bad after
all. What are we gonna do?!
I don't know.
I've never burned a car before.
This is terrible!
We failed him!
The shame!
Can't ever show our
faces again!
We need to hide away
forever!
Ooh, dark. Filthy. Horrible.
Perfect. >> My car!
Who did this?!
Those kids!
I'm gonna get them for this!
Come out!
I'm calling the sheriff!
No!
They know we wrecked the car.
What do you mean you
wrecked the car?
Aaah!
Dad? Hi. ♪ Daisy
Daisy the donkey ♪
mom?
Why are the Robinsons talking to
the sheriff on our lawn?
I don't know, sweetie.
I think we'll just go around the
back.
I tell you, sheriff, it was
those kids next door, as sure as
i... What? We just touched it
with the sponge and it fell
apart, so we decided to hide
here forever.
Such a sad story. But it's not true!
You see, it was 9:00 this
morning, and blhlhlhlhlhlhlh.
Now come on, electrofat.
Make me beautiful! Whoo!
Aah! Aaaaaaah! You... Thing of... Beauty!
Mr. Robinson's new car.
Okay.
It's just a dink.
I'll bang it out. This may take a while.
There! Finished! Aah!
Blhlhlhlhlh.
So, you see, it was my fault,
not yours. What sound we do now?
Well, i think the most
responsible thing to do is to
hide here forever
And never let your mother find
out what happened.
I already
know. Aaaaah! Honey?
But it's not quite what
you think.
It was 9:00 this morning, and...
Wait! Can i do this? Blhlhlhlhlh!
♪ Daisy ♪
put the tape on, mom!
Yes, honey.
♪ Donkey Daisy ♪ Where is it? Here.
Yeah! They parked right in front of
our lawn.
I just didn't see it.
I was about to tell
Mr. Robinson, but... Horrible mother...
So, we went to see the show.
And it was great!
So, there.
It was mostly my fault.
I'm so relieved.
It was a family effort!
Darn it!
I know they're up there!
Get in there and arrest those
vandals!
Not without a warrant, sir.
Aaaaah!
I pay my taxes, and that pays
your salary!
Ergo, I'm your boss!
Now get in there and do your
job!
Please, sir! Calm down! >> All right.
I supposed i shall have to take
matters into my own hands?!
Well...
Here come the Robinsons.
Poor Mr. Robinson.
We wrecked his beautiful new
car, and nobody has the courtesy
to apologize.
We should be ashamed
of ourselves!
So, let's get out
there and apologize, as a
family. Okay.
This is what happens when you
mess with gaylord!
This is what happens!
This... Is... What... Happens!
They look kind of angry,
gumball.
Please, stop! Please!
Please, ma'am. Drop the duster!
Please! No, ma'am!
No! No! >> Aaah!
Margaret! >> No, sir! No, please!
Aah!
Maybe we should give
them time to calm down.
[ Shouting
[ indistinctly ]
So, do you want to press
charges?
No, I'm sure they learned their lesson.
It's too bad you have to live
next to such monsters.
don't worry,
Mr. Robinson.
We'll look out for your house
while you're gone!
Aaaah!
Such a great guy.
Well, there's one
important thing we learned
today. That electrofat machine
was worth every penny.
Anais, for the last
time, we just can't afford it. But why?
Richard, tell your daughter why
we can't go to daisyland.
We're going to
daisyland?! No! But why?
Because money doesn't
grow on trees and daisyland
tickets don't just fall from the
But you always say
that if you put your mind to it,
you can accomplish anything.
Dad, what are you doing?
I'm getting tickets
using the power of my mind.
That's not gonna...
Shh.
I hate to break it to
you guys, but it's not gonna
happen.
The world doesn't work like that.
Gumball watterson, get out of
this bathroom!
♪ today's gonna be a
wonderful day 'cause i got in
the shower first ♪
♪ la la-la la-la-la-la-la ♪
Aah!
Whaaaaa! Whoa!
Wait for us!
Wait for us! Wait for us! Rocky!
Hold up! Wait for me!
Rocky?
Rocky!! Owwwwwww!
Well, it seems like it's not my
day, but that's okay, because
it's nothing a good song won't
fix.
♪ when life hands you lemons,
you got to make some lemonade ♪
Darwin, stop it
already. It's getting embarrassing.
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Gumball! How's it going?! It's great...
Except for the fact that this is
starting out to be the worst day
of my life!
It's like I'm cursed or something.
Watterson!
This school has a dress code.
These rags are obscene!
Get to lost and found.
They'll provide you with
something more suitable.
But principal brown... >> now!
There you go. Much better.
You've got to be
kidding me.
I'm sorry, dude, but this
isn't a department store, you
know.
Rocky.
There's got to be something else.
You're in luck!
People think I'm a fruit,
but I'm also classified as an herb.
What? Where did you get your clothes,
lost and found?! Well, actually, yes,
i did. >> Hey, where did you get your
clothes, the circus?! Dude, we kind of
just went over this already...
lost and found.
>>.
Hey, where did you get your
clothes, the swim shop and the
hat shop?!
Where did you get your brain
from, the dollar store?!
Seven hours detention for
hurting my feelings.
What?! But...
I'll see you after school.
Fine! Paper cut!
Gumball, are you
okay?
Everything's great,
Darwin. Everything's just peachy. Okay!
Darwin!
don't take everything i say so
literally!
Okay. What about what you just said now?
Should i take that literally?
No... yes!
No.
I don't know. Talk to me.
I think I'm cursed.
Then what you need is a good
luck charm.
Guys, there are no
such things as lucky charms,
curses, or tickets falling from
the sky.
There must be a scientific
explanation for what's happening
to gumball, like there is for
everything.
Yeah?
How does your science explain
the magical rainbows, then?
Diffraction of light
through moisture in the
atmosphere. It's a sad world you live in.
Come on, gumball.
Darwin, how will i
know if it's a 4-leaf clover?
Simple.
They've got four leaves and
they're extremely rare.
Rare? They're one in a million!
Rarer that the rarest...
found one!
Top 'o the morning to ya!
Ooh. I can already feel my luck changing.
- Hey, look!
- A lucky fo...
I'm ready to take
your advice now.
I knew you'd come
around eventually.
Now, please tell me.
What's the scientific
explanation for all of this?!
There's no
explanation.
What's been happening is just a
coincidental series of
unfortunate events.
Look, I'm just gonna have to show you.
Okay, opening an umbrella
indoors, breaking a mirror, and
walking under a ladder are all
considered to bring extremely
bad luck.
Ha! Nonsense.
And to prove this, you're going
to perform all three tasks at
the same time.
You sure about this?
Mathematically, the
chance of anything else
happening to you is miniscule. Okay.
Here goes!
Wow. I guess you were right.
I guess logic and
reason just went down the drain.
Hey, guys! Guys!
I've been thinking
scientifically, and i think i
figured it out!
Yesterday evening, gumball and i
were setting the table for dinner...
Whoa!
Wow.
It was probably the
luckiest thing i have ever seen.
So, according to my findings,
gumball used up all his good
luck in one day, and that's why
today he's left with nothing but
bad luck!
Of course!
That doesn't make sense, but
it's the best we got.
So, the logical conclusion to
your nonsensical theory is that
if he can survive today,
everything should be back to
normal by tomorrow!
Of course!
I'll be right back, watterson.
I've got some important business
to attend to.
What?! No!
Don't leave me!
You're staying right there
because you're in detention!
No!
You don't understand!
I'm in great danger!
You're in great danger of
getting another three hours
detention!
Principal brown! Please!
I got to get out of here!
No, wait!
Just do nothing.
Just do nothing. Just do...
Sorry, i forgot to slam the
door in anger!
Aah!
Okay, i think i might go and do
nothing somewhere else!
I'm so glad i confiscated this.
Watterson!
What are... Aah!
Come on, bad luck!
Let's get this over with!
Give me your best shot!
Raaaaaaaaaah!
No! No!
Okay! Sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm alive!
Aaaaah!
Aw, give me a break!
Aah! Aah! Aaaah!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
- In your face, bad luck!
- I am invinci...!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
No, i can make this! I'm gonna make it!
I'm gonna make it!
I'm not gonna make it!
- What happened?
- The doctor says you were
very lucky to survive... very
lucky indeed.
Lucky?
This means my good luck has
finally returned!
Thus proving my
scientific hypothesis to be
- correct.
- And since science and
reason have gone out the window,
i suggest we use the power of
our minds to get tickets for daisyland.
One family pass to daisyland, please.
No! My... my ticket! D'
Well, i wonder to where the wind
will take it.
Hey, a daisyland ticket!
I wonder to where the wind will take it.
Look, mother.
A daisyland ticket.
Mother, I'm wondering to where
the wind will take it.
Yay! I wished for snow!