Is that you, tooth fairy?
Aaaah! It's a ghost!
It's a ghost! It's a gho...
Mom! I need more!
- But that's your fifth
Well, it's because, i-I'm... Growing?
Well, could you try and grow slower?
This is costing me a fortune.
Thanks. Richard,
what are you doing in the cupboard?
Shhhh! I'm hiding from the ghost.
This house is haunted!
Okay. Heh. I'm closing the door now.
Thanks, mom.
What are you doing?
Follow me and all will be revealed.
I have got something amazing to show you.
Whoa! A sheet! No, Darwin.
Something even better.
Mr. Robinson? Yep.
I found him in the shed, so i
put him up here in the attic, where I've
provided him with full en suite dining,
unlimited
beverages, and a queen-size bed.
Anais: You
do realize what keeping
a 50-year-old man in
these conditions is called?
Love? Kidnapping.
- And i want nothing more to do with it.
- Don't worry,
- Mr. Robinson. We will never abandon you.
- What was he doing in
the shed? Gumball: I don't know.
He hasn't said a word since i
He looks kind of... Broken.
It's okay, Mr. Robinson.
I know just what will cheer you
up. And now, ladies and gentlemen,
for tonight only, i give you...
Me! Darwin: Whoa!
This guy's good! Gumball: Ho-okay, okay.
Now, what do you call... This?!
That's right... a pea on a fork.
His head is the pea. His head is the pea!
And now, what's
this?! It's a butt... In an elevator.
Why? Wh-h-h-y?!
Wh-h-h-h-h-h-h-y?! Dad: Aaah!
E-e-e-nough! You can ruin my sleep,
you can terrorize my family,
but you will not stop me
from eating my sausage!
Cheer up,
Mr. Robinson. You know what
i do when I'm feeling a bit low?
I look at this.
Hey! Look what i found! ♪ electrofat ♪
♪ get you fit while you watch
TV ♪ i think this may help.
It says here "promotes health and
happiness. Side effects may include
electrocution, hair loss,
hair gain, depression,
euphoria, blackouts, amnesia," blah blah
blah blah blah... aha! "Gets results fast"!
- Well, this is exactly
Okay, now power it up.
Look! He's moving!
It's working!
He's asking for more! Turn it up!
He's smiling! He's smiling!
Richard, what are you
doing... aaah! Dad: Aah! Nicole! Nicole!
Nicole! Where are you?!
Nicole!! Mom: I'm here.
Richard, can you tell me
why I'm hanging upside-down?
Because this place is
haunted, and i need to set more traps!
Does he look happy?
- Nah, he looks more
like a bulldog staring at the sun.
don't you think?
Yeah. Let's try to remember the last
time he looked happy. Yeah.
That was the day you learned how
to tie your shoelaces.
It hurts!
The smile on his face.
I'll treasure that memory forever.
That's it, Darwin. He finds
happiness in the suffering of others.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Hey, Mr. Robinson.
Look at this.
It's funny 'cause it hurts!
Right, Mr. Robinson?
You have to put more heart into it.
Like this!
Ooh! Unh!
Richard, honey,
can you help me down, please?
Don't you understand?!
We're at war! I've already lost one
sausage, and i will not lose another one.
- But who are you fighting?
- The ghost, of course!
Hey, Mr. Robinson, look.
Is he smiling yet?
- Nope.
Richard. Richard! Please look at me!
- First he takes my
sausages, and then what? Should i let him
take my wife? A man's house is his castle,
Nicole. And this is a castle,
and I'm not letting him ruin it.
There's a phantom in our bed,
and before you know it...
Richard, by all means,
be hysterical,
but please don't forget to breathe.
A giant earwig!
And the next thing you know,
he'll come for the kids... the
kids!
Mom: There are no such things as ghosts.
Richard, calm down.
Dad: You calm down, Nicole!
Richard, please don't...
Margaret and i used to argue like that...
sometimes up to six
times a day, from first thing in
the morning until last thing at night.
In the kitchen,
in the backyard, in the car,
occasionally, we'd do it in public,
once even while
- we were sleeping.
- But what happened?
I don't know. Something changed.
And one day, she said the spark
had gone and asked me to leave.
- That's when you found me in the shed.
- So that's what's
wrong with Mr. Robinson.
He lost his anger. Look!
- Yeah, that looks more like it.
- We're gonna sort
this out. How? Gumball: Leave that to us.
- But first, we got to get you out of here.
- Breathe in, breathe out.
Breathe in, breathe out.
Are you sure about this?
Don't worry. You're in safe hands. Ready?
- Breathe in, breathe... aaaaah!
- Aaaaaah!
Enough!
Heh!
I'm not sure what he sees in that woman,
but anyway...
Come on, Mr. Robinson!
Let's show her you still got it!
Okay, now go ballistic. I can't, kids.
I'm not that man anymore.
Then we'll do it for you.
Hey, you! Mr. Robinson's wife!
Come and have an argument with him!
I mean... Me! We're gonna have a fight,
and you're gonna like it!
Ha! How do you like my arguing,
See how angry i am?!
Wanna make out?
You made it worse. I didn't think it
was possible, but you made it worse.
Waaah! The ghost!
He's about to attack the
- children! Aaaaah!
- Aaaaaaaah!
This is for attacking my kids!
And this... Is... For... My...
- Sausage! Gumball: Dad!
- Now get out of my
garden! Gumball: Stop it!
It's Mr. Robinson!
Sorry!
Uuuuuuuuuuugh!
Dad: Show yourself, ghost of Mr. Robinson!
Hey, what's up, neighbor?
I've had enough of this family!
Your tacky lifestyle, your ugly
house, your cheap garden shed!
I'll smash it to pieces!
It's more solid than i thought.
But this is what i do to your
unfashionable deck chairs! Unh! Uggh!
Gosh darn it! And as for your crummy
thrift store vacuum cleaner buy cheap...
Buy twice!
And this is what i think
of your $2 clip-on tie!
I'm back! And as for you...
Yay! Welcome back, Mr. Robinson!
So, since we saved your
marriage and everything, i
guess that makes us best friends forever?
- So can we call you
gaylord instead of Mr. Robinson? don't
push it, kid. Now, take me home, woman.
What was that all about?
Well, there never was a ghost, dad.
- It was Mr. Robinson.
- We hid him in the attic.
No. I mean, what's wrong with our house,
our shed, and my tie?
Dad, you know what i do when i
feel like a loser? I look at this.
Yeah. I feel better now.
W-who does he think he is, anyway?
"$2 clip-on tie."
At least i know how to treat my wife!
Unh!
Aaaaah! Richard!!
How can you take Darwin away from us?
Well,
it seems he scored 100% on his aptitude
test. This has never happened before,
so i had to tell the government. Gumball:
The government? Yes, they want to test him
out, study his brain, probe it,
dissect it... that kind of thing.
Please resolve the following
equation using the marker pen
Hmmmm.
It's best they take him away.
He'd make the rest of you feel
I guess he's got a point.
So, you put clever people in quarantine
like they're some sort of contagious
pathological disease?
Maybe there's more than one
What i meant was...
Phbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbhhhttt! ♪ la, la,
la, la, la, la, la, la,
la, la, la, la, la ♪
phbt! Phbt! Phbt! Apparently not.
What makes you think I'll
let you take away my son?
Well, technically, you're not his parents.
He's registered as a...
Richard, what are we going to do?
Get a new pet fish?
Dad: I'll save you, my little fish boy!
Mr. watterson,
that is a stationary closet.
- Can we visit him?
- Are you saying we'll
- never see Darwin again?
- Then I'll go with
him by proving i am a genius, too!
I need to become intelligent right now!
Quick, gumball...
to the liberray! The libararara!
The... Libarium?
The place where all the nerds hang out.
I had so much more love to give!
- No one will ever be able
- to replace him. Hey, dudes.
- Hi, rocky.
What's with the suitcase?
I kind of got rent
troubles, and i don't want to stay at my
parents'. Hey! Can i crash at your place?
Please?
Oooh!
Gumball: I got to find something that
Will make me smart.
What do you reckon, Darwin?
Look... salsola collina,
more commonly known as Russian thistle,
wind witch, or, if
you're really stupid, a tumbleweed.
That's it! I need a bigger head.
Inconceivable.
Maths will always hold a special
place in my timetable.
Greetings, fellow crusader of knowledge.
What's your favorite subject?
Calculus?
Trigonometry?
Come on. Spit it out.
That guy is such a
gluteus Maximus.
Hey, bobert. Whatcha doin'?
I'm on the Internet, the
largest source of knowledge in the world.
Why don't you get connected?
Hi. Hello? Is that the Internet?
You need to click the icon.
Gumball: Ooh, you need to click the icon.
Which one is the icon?
Dude, it's the only thing on
- I - knew that.
Whoooooooa!
It's beautiful! I can feel it!
I'm totally learning
somethi-ing-ing-ing-ing-ing!
What... Happened?
Your memory could not cope.
- You crashed. I had to reboot you.
- Come on!
There's got to be something in
this library making people smart.
This is such a great book!
I'd like to borrow this book, please.
Book? Book book book! Book book!
Oooh.
That's it! They're all watching books.
Hey. Shh! Gumball: Hey!
Shhhh! Gumball: Hey! Shhhhhhhh!
I think my book is broken.
I've been watching it for ages,
and I'm still not smart.
You don't watch books. You read them.
Shh! People are trying to work.
Okay, brain, let's get reading.
Once... U-pon... A... Ti-i-i-me...
that's it. I'm out of here.
I've had enough. I'm off to watch TV.
Hey! Where do you think you're going?
I didn't sign up for this.
I quit! Gumball: You can't quit.
There's no way I'm gonna pass a
test without a brain. Please.
I need you. We'll never pass.
Then...
then I'm going to make you smart, like
Darwin! >> sir? You appear to have a bit
of... Ink on your face.
Are you sure there's
nothing else you want, honey?
Ask for anything.
Well, can i have two cans of soda?
- Quick, Richard... the
fridge! And some jelly beans.
But only the yellow ones!
Dad: Okay! Are you sure there's
- nothing else to wear, Mrs. watterson?
- Please, honey... you can
- call us "mom" and "dad."
- Read it! I can't!
Read it! So difficult! don't make me!
Aren't you tired of being so useless?
Years and years of insults and
abuse. Remember... Another "f" for you,
pea brain! Doofus! Loser!
- Okay, I'm ready.
- Then prove it.
- Hyah!
- This may take a
while. Ooph!
♪ I was a feeble-minded guy ♪ ♪
I'd slip on ice and wonder why ♪
♪ so many obstacles were thrown my
way ♪ ♪ on a downward slide each and
every day ♪ ♪ but something
popped inside my brain ♪
♪ i got up to fight that fight again
♪ ♪ and i knew what to do ♪
♪ i went through the mental
pain ♪ ♪ you gotta think big ♪
♪ think deep ♪ ♪ pretty soon,
you'll make that quantum leap ♪
♪ think big ♪ ♪ think smart ♪
♪ make your brain your finest
body part ♪ ♪ the greatest
minds from yesterday ♪
♪ will be crushed to dust 'cause
I'm on my way ♪ ♪ think big, big ♪
♪ you gotta think big ♪
- Aah!
- I want to take the
aptitude test!
You don't have the brain of a
- genius, watterson.
- We'll see about that.
Come on, brain...
show principal brown what you can do.
What the... what is wrong with you?!
I meant do an equation or something.
Sorry.
I always pictured it a little smaller.
I've been working out.
Hey, dudes, want some popcorn?
Dad, can i borrow mom's car
tonight? Dad: Sure, son.
Anything you like.
Man, my dad is a righteous dude.
Mom? What's going on here?
- .
Well, this is your new brother...
rockwin. 'Sup?
You're kidding, right?
- Come on.
Let's just all give it a try.
Just for a moment.
It's not working! You're right. It's not.
Just a minute! No, it's not working.
I miss Darwin so much!
- All right! It was me!
- What? - It was me who filled
out Darwin's aptitude test. I found it on
the TV guide. I should be the one who gets
So Darwin's not a genius?
Darwin!
Hello. We believe this is yours.
- Yay! Welcome back, buddy.
- We missed you so much.
- Don't ever go away again.
- What a conveniently
happy ending. Not so fast.
Hey! I said it was a happy ending!
You still owe us one genius.
What do you mean? Well,
it's obvious he didn't take that test.
But someone in this house did,
and this warrant says that
we get to take that person away.
Who is it?
I know who it is.
Be quiet! don't listen to him.
He's insane in the membrane.
- Don't worry. I know what I'm doing.
- No, you don't!
You're stupid! We've established that!
Let the brain speak.
Sorry. The person who took the test
was...
H-h-h-h-h-h-h-h-h-h-h-h-h-h-h... him!
Rocky? Me?
Yeah, i took that test.
Then get your suitcase.
You're coming to the research center.
What, you mean, like, for free?
Well, of course.
Definitely beats my parents' place.
And I'm gonna need a hot
tub, too... 'cause i do most
of my thinking in the bath.
See ya, rocky!
Bye, rocky! So long!
That was really smart, brain.
Darwin's back home. Can i come home, too?
Are you kidding me?
Get in there, little dude. Whoo-hoo!
High five! Ha! And a pepperoni pizza?
Then will you solve the equation?
Yeah, yeah.
After my pedicure.