[ Upbeat music plays ]
Gumball: Please, mom!
Both: Please!
Darwin: S'il te plait?
Gumball: Por favor?
Darwin: Bitte?
Gumball: We really want to do
karate.
Both: 'Olu'olu?
Mom: [ Sighs ]
Okay.
Both: Yay!
Mom: You better not get bored
and give it up right away.
Gumball: Mom, when have we
ever given something up?
Both: I hate football!
I hate tennis!
I hate flippin' horses!
Gumball: I hate figure
skating!
Oh, yeah.
Mom: Promise me you'll go to
the lessons this time.
Gumball: [ Scoffs ]
Who needs lessons?
You already bought us
black belts.
[ Ka-ching! ]
Mom: [ Sighs ]
Darwin: Dude, you look so
powerful in your belt.
Gumball: You too, man.
Darwin: Really?
Gumball: Yeah.
You're, like, half shark, half
bear, half alligator.
Darwin: Shark/bear/gator.
Gumball: Darwin, let's agree
to never take these off.
Darwin: Agreed!
Gumball: Hyah!
Ooh-yah! Wah!
Hyah!
Darwin: Yah!
Wah-ah!
[ Munches ]
Gumball: [ Grunting ]
Come on! Hyah!
Darwin: [ Grunting ]
[ School bell rings ]
That was the best day of my
life!
Yah! Yah! Yah!
[ Laughter ]
Why don't you fight Tina?
Gumball: No, no, no, no.
Our karate is strictly for
self-defense.
Darwin: To misuse the power
in this fin would bring terrible
dishonor upon our dojo.
[ Laughs ] Do another flip!
[ Laughter ]
Gumball: All right, just one
more -- for the fans.
[ Inhales deeply ]
Darwin: Awesome!
[ Laughter ]
Uncool!
Mom: Boys, come on!
Time to go!
Gumball: One second, mom!
Hey, penny! Hyah!
What do you think of my new
style?
Hmm. Very, um...
Gumball: Impressive?
Well...
I like to see you happy.
Gumball: Thanks. Wah!
You need to work on that
defense, young lotus.
Farewell.
[ Car door opens, closes ]
Hyah! You flinched!
Mom: [ Chuckles nervously ]
Everything okay at school,
honey?
Gumball: Yeah, school is
awesome, especially when you're
wearing one of these.
Mom: It's just that it kind
of looked like the kids were
making fun of you back there.
Gumball: Yeah, laughing with
you can sound like laughing at
you.
Darwin: They even called us
the karate wieners!
Gumball: I think it's because
we always "win" at karate.
[ Chuckles ]
The perfect karate master.
Dad: [ Laughs ]
[ Grunts, laughs ]
In your face! [ Laughs ]
[ Sighs ]
I wish i could kick people like
this in real life.
Hey, nice costumes, guys.
You have a spare one?
Gumball: Nah, sorry, dad.
I'm not sure you're ready for
the responsibility.
Dad: [ Sighs ] I understand.
Gumball: Come on, Darwin.
Let's go practice some killer
moves.
Okay, you know what a true
warrior needs for a good
warm-up?
Darwin: Mittens and a scarf?
Gumball: No, Darwin-San.
[ Rock music playing ]
Inspiration.
Both: ¶ every time i look in
the mirror ¶
¶ all i see is the inner
warrior ¶
¶ staring back at me ¶
mom: Oh, Richard, I'm so
worried about them.
¶ Warrior ¶
¶ inner warrior ¶
dad: What?
It's a great track.
Mom: They're obsessed with
those outfits, and the kids at
school are making fun of them.
You know how mean kids can be.
¶ ...The best that you can
be ¶
mom: Richard?
Hmph!
I know they're just costumes,
but if people make fun of them,
they'll never get girlfriends or
a job, and in 20 years' time,
they'll still be living here and
wearing those ridiculous karate
outfits!
[ Video game beeping ]
Darwin: Gumball.
Gumball: Yeah?
Darwin: I think we've wasted
our lives.
[ "Character dying" sound ]
Gumball: Yah!
Darwin: Yah, yah, yah!
Mom: Boys.
Both: Hi, mom.
Gumball: Check out Darwin's
sweet scissor kick.
Darwin: Hyah!
Mom: When did you post this?
Gumball: We didn't.
Some kids at school did.
Mom: Boys, look at the
title -- "tae-Kwon dorks."
I think they might be making fun
of you.
Gumball: Nah.
They just spelled "tae Kwon do"
wrong.
Darwin: Korean spelling is
very complicated.
Gumball: There's loads of
other fellow senseis on here.
Look.
Yah!
Gumball: Hey!
Mom: [ Sighs ]
I need to tell you a story.
Gumball: Cool!
Is it a fable about a great
martial-arts warrior?
Mom: Not exactly.
When your father was at school,
he thought he was the
cottontail cavalier.
Dad: ...Cavalier!
[ Humming ]
[ Laughter ]
Costumed geek!
Leave him alone!
At least he's brave enough to be
himself!
He was lucky there was one girl
who loved him for who he really
was.
Darwin: What a sad story.
Gumball: But what ever
happened to the cape?
Mom: Well, i managed to get
it off him and hide it.
Dad: What?!
You mean the president didn't
really need my cape?!
Mom: I'm sorry, honey.
Dad: [ Gasps ]
It's because of you I'm mortal!
[ Crying ]
Mom: [ Sighs ] You see?
That's the kind of state you can
get into when you refuse to grow
up.
Darwin: Gumball, i don't want
to be a costumed geek.
Gumball: It's okay, Darwin.
Mom, we'll stop wearing the
outfits if it'll make you happy.
Mom: Thank you, boys.
I'm so proud of you.
You'll see -- it's for the best.
Gumball: ¶ life's a battle of
abandoning ¶
¶ dream after dream ¶
Darwin: ¶ hopes and
expectations ¶
¶ float way downstream ¶
gumball: ¶ it's time to kiss
our childish ways goodbye ¶
Darwin: What?
Give mediocrity a try?
Gumball: ¶ the games, they
have to stop ¶
Darwin: ¶ no more hyah ¶
gumball: ¶ not even a karate
chop ¶
both: ¶ face up to what
maturity means ¶
¶ and forget about our
martial-arts dre-e-e-e-e-e-ams ¶
[ both sigh ]
Gumball: Well, i think I'm
cured.
Darwin: Me too.
I almost think i could put it
back on, you know, just one last
time and I'd be fine.
Gumball: I reckon if i put
mine back on, it would do
nothing.
[ Both laugh ]
Oh, it feels so good.
[ Door opens ]
Mom: Boys, is that you?
Gumball: U-uh, yeah.
Just rushing off to school.
You know, don't want to miss any
of those, uh, spelling...Sums.
Mom: That's great, honey.
Now, where did you put those
karate costumes?
Gumball: Those old things?
I completely forgot about them.
Mom: But you had them only
yesterday.
Gumball: That was yesterday?!
Well, time sure flies when
you're all grown up.
Can you remember where we put
them?
Darwin: Beats me.
Gumball: Maybe they're in the
closet.
Bye!
Mom: Bye.
And now to get rid of this
problem once and for all.
What the -- they're gone!
Wait a minute.
Gumball: Bye!
[ Distorted ] Bye!
By-y-y-y-y-e!
Mom: Those little fibbers!
Gumball: Okay, let's get
these dorky clothes off.
Darwin: I don't know.
I think I'm gonna keep mine on.
Gumball: What?!
Darwin: Mom's kind of right.
This is a bit lame.
Gumball: Are you crazy?!
[ Grunting ]
Is that lame?
Darwin: Nah.
It's pretty awesome.
Gumball: Exactly!
Now, our fans are waiting.
The karate wieners have
returned!
[ Laughter ]
People, please, contain your
excitement.
At lunch break, come and see me
attempt the impossible.
What, are you gonna get a
girlfriend?
[ Laughter ]
Gumball: No.
I'm going to break 12 planks of
wood with this hand!
Darwin: Are you crazy?
Gumball: No, Darwin.
I'm more sane than I've ever
been!
Mom: I can't believe they
lied to me!
I never should've given them
those outfits!
What was i thinking?!
[ Horn honks ]
Out of my way!
My kids are in danger!
Of becoming their father!
[ Gong rings ]
Darwin: Dude, seriously, how
are you gonna do this?
Gumball: Easy -- I've seen
loads of guys do it on the
Internet.
All i have to do is hit it with
my hand.
Watch.
Karate fans, please, can i have
a little hush?
Yeah, quiet!
I want to hear him fail!
[ Laughter ]
Darwin: Shh!
Gumball: Thank you,
Darwin-San.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Hyah!
[ Squeaks ]
[ Laughter ]
Stop laughing!
don't you guys watch TV?
When you believe in yourself,
you can accomplish anything!
[ Crying ] Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
Hyah! Hyah! Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
[ Muffled ] Oh, man, it looked
easier on the Internet.
Maybe I'll just do one plank.
[ Breathing heavily ]
Hyah!
[ Grunts ]
[ Crying ]
Ow.
[ Laughter ]
Ladies and gentlemen, the
karate wiener!
[ Laughter ]
Gumball: Hang on.
"Wiener" doesn't mean "winner."
It means "sausage."
[ Crying ]
[ Laughter continues ]
Mom: Oh, no! I'm too late!
Hey, leave him alone!
If he wants to wear karate
clothes, let him!
At least he's brave enough to be
himself!
Mom: [ Gasps ]
Besides, i think he looks...
Cute, kind of like a-a...
Darwin: Shark/bear/gator?
Yeah, something like that.
Gumball: I told you girls
would dig it.
Thanks for sticking up for me,
penny.
My pleasure, gumball-San.
Wah! Hah!
[ Both laugh ]
[ Gong rings ]
Mom: Oh, my little karate
wiener's in love.
[ Video game beeping ]
Richard.
Dad: Yeah?
Mom: The president wants you
to have this back.
Dad: Aaaaaaah!
Really?!
I can feel its power!
Mom: Well, put it on.
Dad: Yes!
The cottontail cavalier has
returned!
[ Humming ]
[ Laughs ]
Ah, just like old times.
Mom: [ Laughs ]
[ Smooches ]
Dad: Oh, thanks, honey.
Dad: [ Grunting ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
We should...Really get an
escalator.
Mom: I told you -- i already
asked Santa.
Dad: Cool!
Mom: Now, kids, while we're
gone, i want you to do what your
granny jojo tells you.
All: Yes, mom.
Dad: [ Grunting ]
Mom: Richard, those go in the
trunk!
Dad: Huh?
What does it look like I'm
doing?!
Mom: That's the gas tank!
[ Laughter ]
Stop laughing at your father.
He tries very hard.
Dad: [ Grunts ]
Mom: That's the glove box!
Dad: Sorry!
[ Laughter ]
Gumball: Mom, I've been
talking it over with Darwin, and
i think I'm old enough not to
have granny jojo kiss me on the
cheek anymore.
Mom: Why don't you want your
granny jojo to kiss you on the
cheek?
Gumball: I'm just not into
the whole kissing-on-the-cheek
thing.
Mom: But she's your
granny jojo.
Gumball: So?
Can't we just shake hands?
Mom: She's your grandmother,
and you're going to let her kiss
you on the cheek!
Between that and her TV
programs, that's all she has
left these days.
Darwin: I like getting kissed
on the cheek.
It makes me feel special.
Anais: He's right, gumball.
It's not the end of the world.
Gumball: Well, if getting
kissed on the cheek is so great,
how come those two always take
off before granny jojo arrives?
Dad: Hurry, Richard!
She'll be here any minute!
Dad: I know! I know!
Mom: Richard, come on!
Dad: Aah!
[ Slurping ]
[ Lips smacking ]
Gumball: [ Groans ]
Anais: Granny jojo!
Hello, dear.
[ Smooches ]
Get my bags, would ya?
Darwin: Granny jojo!
Hello, walking fish.
[ Smooches ]
Where's the blue one?
Gumball: Here i am.
Anais: [ Breathing heavily ]
Say my name.
Gumball: [ Sighs ]
Anais: Come on, gumball.
Just get it over with.
Gumball: Well, it's easy for
you --
[ Smooches ]
Gumball: Aah!
Hurry up with those bags,
anais.
I don't want to miss the
"sheriff mcgruff" marathon.
He's the only man of justice in
a world of deceit.
Anais: [ Grunting ]
Darwin: See?
That wasn't so bad.
Gumball?
Gumball, are you okay?
Gumball: [ Squeaks ]
Anais: [ Grunting ]
Darwin: Anais?
Anais: I'm kind of busy here.
Darwin: Something's wrong
with gumball.
Gumball: [ Squeaking ] She --
she -- she kissed me!
She kissed me!
Anais: She kisses all of us!
Get over it!
[ Grunts ]
Geez! What's in this thing --
bowling balls?
[ Grunting ]
Darwin: You okay, buddy?
Anais: Aah! Look out!
[ Squish ]
Gumball: Aah!
[ Breathing heavily ]
Anais!
You be careful with
granny jojo's bag.
Anais: Yes, granny jojo.
Darwin, you're getting me in
trouble.
Take care of gumball.
Darwin: Hmm.
Hey, i know.
Let's go to your happy place.
Gumball: My happy place?
Darwin: Yeah, you know, that
special place you go to when you
feel bad.
Gumball: I don't have a happy
place!
Where's your happy place?
Darwin: Everywhere's my happy
place.
[ Birds chirping ]
Hi, mailbox!
Hi, Darwin!
Darwin: Hi, tree!
Hey, Darwin!
Darwin: Hey, dangerous
criminal!
What?!
Oh, heya, Darwin.
[ Car alarm blaring ]
Darwin: Hi, two rats eating a
kabob!
Both: Hi, Darwin!
Darwin: Hi, $100 bill!
Hello, Darwin!
Darwin: Hi, grumpy old guys!
Hey, i hear your grandma's in
town!
Give her a big kiss from me!
Gumball: [ Whimpers ]
Find your happy place,
find your happy place.
Darwin: Here you go.
Gumball: Thanks.
Darwin: [ Slurping ]
[ Smooches ]
Gumball: Aah!
Darwin: Find your happy
place.
Find your h--
oh, hey, look -- a butterfly!
Gumball: Ohhhhh. Pretty.
Give granny jojo a kiss!
Gumball: Aah!
Happy place! H-h-happy, happy!
Darwin: Come here and smell
these flowers.
[ Sniffing ] Mmm!
Daffodils!
Gumball: [ Sniffs ]
Hmm.
They kind of smell like...
Granny jojo!
[ Sighs ]
Aw. Why so sad?
You need to find your happy
place!
Gumball: There is no happy
[ Sobbing ]
I'm sorry, little creature!
[ Both crying ]
Darwin: I'm sorry i couldn't
help you forget!
[ Crying continues ]
[ All crying ]
[ Music playing on TV ]
[ Music stops ]
Anais!
Anais!!
Anais: Yes, granny jojo?
Did you take granny jojo's
bag up to her room?
Anais: Almost!
Well, hurry up.
It's almost 4:30.
It's nearly suppertime.
[ Music resumes ]
TV. Yeah.
Anais: This should work.
Darwin: I'll get the door
for you, buddy.
Gumball: Oh, thanks.
Aah!
[ Muffled scream ]
Darwin: Eat up, gumball.
Dinner will take your mind off
it.
Anais: [ Slurping loudly ]
[ Lips smacking ]
[ Slurping ]
Gumball: Darwin?
Aah!
[ Screaming ]
Aaaaaaaah!
Aaaaaaah!
[ Screaming ]
Aaaaaaaaaah!
Oh.
Oh, man, that was intense.
Give us a kiss!
Gumball: No!!
Anais: Aah!
Darwin: Aah!
Gumball: [ Panting ]
Anais: Oh, come on!
That's the fifth time tonight!
Gumball: What are you doing
out there?
Anais: Trying to move this
stupid bag!
[ Grunting ]
Darwin: Gumball, maybe you'll
never get over that kiss.
Anais: Then you need to fight
fire with fire!
Darwin: Won't that burn the
house down?
Anais: No, no, no.
I mean, you've got to go through
something much worse to forget
about grandma's kisses.
[ Grunting ]
Darwin: [ Gasps ]
Trauma therapy!
[ Indistinct shouting ]
Gumball: What if this doesn't
work, Darwin?
Darwin: Oh, it'll work.
It has to.
All: [ Chanting ] You're
gonna squirm, cry, sweat, and
scream!
You're gonna squirm, cry, sweat,
and scream!
Gumball: Uh...
Darwin: Come on, gumball,
this is gonna be bad!
I can't hear you!
Gumball: I didn't say
anything!
Darwin: I said, "are you
ready?"
Gumball: No, you didn't!
Darwin: Oh. Are you ready?
Gumball: Yes.
Darwin: Run that way!
Gumball: [ Grunts ]
[ Grunts ]
Darwin: Welcome to level 1,
the leap of [Echoing] faith.
Gumball: Leap of faith.
Eh. Sounds easy enough.
[ Grunts ]
[ All gasp ]
Darwin: Oh.
Did i say "the leap of faith"?
I meant "the leap of filth"!
Gumball: Aaaaaaaaaah!
All: Ew!
Ohh!
Gumball: You're enjoying
this, aren't you?
Darwin: Uh-huh.
Forgotten about the kiss yet?
Gumball: No.
Darwin: On your feet,
gumball.
You really stink.
But you're in luck!
You're gonna take a shower.
To level 2!
The shower of slime!
Gumball: [ Inhales deeply ]
[ Giggles ]
Darwin: Forgotten yet?
Gumball: About what?
Darwin: About the kiss.
Gumball: Oh.
I had, but you just reminded me.
Darwin: Oh.
Then welcome to level 3, the
see-through stuff of sweaty
cheese!
[ All gasp ]
Gumball: [ Gagging ]
[ Gasps ]
Haah!
Darwin: Forgotten yet?
Gumball: No!
[ Panting ]
What are you guys doing here?
We're your next level -- the
"sounds of suffering."
[ Laughs ]
[ Screech! ]
Gumball: [ Groans ]
[ Scrape! Scrape! ]
Aah! Ungh!
Darwin: Forgotten now?
Gumball: No!
Darwin: How about now?
[ Squeak! ]
Gumball: Aah!
Make it sto-o-o-o-p!
[ All cheering ]
[ Panting ]
Darwin: The good news is,
this is the last level.
The bad news is, this is the
worst.
[ Thud! Thud! ]
Gumball: Really?
[ Sighs ] Okay. Do it.
[ Sloop! ]
[ Panting ]
Aah!
[ Thud! ]
[ Grunts ]
Darwin: So?
Gumball: So...What?
[ All gasp ]
Darwin: He's forgotten!
[ All cheering ]
Anais: [ Grunting ]
[ Grunting ]
Aah!
Yes! I did it!
Granny jojo, granny jojo!
I did it!
You did what?
Anais: I carried your
suitcase up to your room.
Oh. Well, good for you, dear.
[ Choir vocalizes ]
Now bring it back down.
My bus will be here any minute.
Gumball: [ Laughs ]
I found my happy place!
Hey, two rats eating a kabob!
Both: Hey, gumball.
Gumball: I found my happy
place.
Ah, that's great.
Good for you, pal.
[ Munch! Munch! Munch! ]
Gumball: Hey, old guy.
No, wait! My back!
Gumball: Whoo-hoo! [ Laughs ]
Oh, that's so much better.
Darwin: Hey, old guy.
[ Crack! ]
Gumball's found his happy place.
Darn it.
Anais, give me a kiss goodbye
and put my bags on the bus.
Anais: [ Grunts ]
[ Smooches ]
A little bit faster this time,
please.
Darwin: Granny jojo!
Gumball's found his happy place!
That's nice, fish kid.
Now kiss me goodbye.
[ Smooches ]
Gumball: Granny jojo!
I found my happy place!
Yeah, whatever.
Now give your granny jojo a kiss
goodbye.
Gumball: Of course.
Anais: Gumball, give me a
hand with this bag!
Gumball: Okay.
[ Smooches ]