And that's why you should
never mix pop rocks and soda.
Okay... Anyone else have a riveting tale?
I do!
Richard, let's hear from the children.
Well, penny asked me out on a date.
No biggie.
She did?! That's great news!
What did she say?
Well... Excuse me... what?!
Do you want to come 'round my
house this Saturday? Me?
With you? At your place?
You see, it's Mr. cuddles'...
Yeah, that's about it.
My little boy is becoming a man.
Mom! Man, you're my hero.
You're going on this big date, and you're
not even nervous! I'd be freaking out!
I mean, think about it... if you blow it, she'll
never speak to you again, and you'll be left
alone for the rest of your life and never
find happiness! don't worry, sweetie.
Just be yourself.
That's all a girl wants.
Thanks, mom. See you after work. Bye!
What? Listen, son,
ignore everything your mother just
said. Why? Look, women only think
they want us to be ourselves because they
don't know how wretched we actually are.
What you have to do is think of someone
really cool and attractive and be them.
R-really? But... but, anais, is this true?
I'm gonna have to go
with dad on this one.
You're kind of a loser, gumball. Exactly.
Sorry. What am i gonna do?
I really like penny.
I want her to like me, too. You could
start by being romantic, dress up a
little, buy her some presents.
Well, i can't do any of those things.
I don't have any money. Listen, son,
you don't need money to show a girl a good
time. You think i have money?...No?
Do you see mom leaving me?
Yeah, every day to
go to work and earn money.
There's other ways to get stuff
without spending money. Do you want to hear
the secrets kept for centuries by watterson
men? I... Don't have any choice, do i?
No! Come with me.
First things first... we need to
get you some nice clothes.
Yeah, penny loves fashion!
That's a great idea! Here we are...
the greatest department store in the
world, where everything is free!
So, anything new?
Whoo! That's nice. What?
You're going to get my date
clothes out of a dump?
Man, that's gross. I didn't hear you
complaining when i gave you that sweater.
What?!
My favorite sweater came out of the dump?!
No.
Don't be silly.
I found it in a sewage outlet. Man.
I wear this all the time.
You are gonna look smashing.
You think so? Right.
You've got the look, but you're
going to need a bit of money in your pocket so
you can treat her on the date, and I'm going to
show you a great way
of getting money for free.
Behold... the credit card!
I simply take this magic card,
insert it like so,
type in the secret magic number that mom
told me, and money comes out of
the little mouth! It works every ti...
choo!
You see? Here you go, son. Awesome!
Hey, hey, beautiful. Hey, penny.
I didn't see you there.
Yeah, i was just passing by...
you know, chillin' with my new hat.
Ha ha. I think I'm ready for my date.
Are you?
Have you even considered how
you're gonna behave on this date?
Yeah, I'm probably gonna be well-behaved.
I mean, like, manners
and etiquette. U... Aah!
Start by pouring Mrs. pumpernickel
a cup of tea. I don't wanna.
Why? 'Cause she's looking at me funny.
See? Gumball, she's a doll.
Why don't you try having a
civilized conversation with her?
All right. So, how was your day,
Mrs. pumpernickel? I see.
Too good to talk to me?
You think you're better than
me with your fancy, little cups and
"la-de-da" friends? Well, you know
nothing about life, Mrs. pumpernickel!
And this is what i do
to your fancy China!
Gumball, just get out of my room.
Okay, so, I'm set.
Got my look, i know where I'm taking her.
I'm ready to go.
There's one thing you're not ready for.
What's that?
This! What was that?
The unexpected,
and you weren't prepared for it.
I-i see what you mean.
Follow me to the training camp.
Where? Just come to the backyard.
You've got to be prepared for anything on
this date, because anything could happen.
Like what?
What if someone tries to mug you?!
I don't know. Call the police?
Wrong. Knock his block off! Enh.
Like that? That was good.
But it's better to finish with a
wisecrack. Women love that. Like what?
Like "welcome to punch town...
population, you." Are you sure this is
gonna help me with my date?
Totally. Okay.
Hi. I'm penny's father, and i don't
approve of you because you don't
have any prospects. Hah!
I'm sorry, daddy, but you're
grounded. Hello.
I'm Sebastian lonkwin,
penny's successful ex-boyfriend. Hah!
Looks like this "ex" is catching some z's.
Is
that all you got?! What do you say to
someone who doesn't believe in love?
Hah! You don't need that heart.
Actually, that was a
little too extreme, but I'll give you
an 8 out of 10. Good job, soldier.
The hardest part of my
job is watching them leave.
So? Son! You look like a million bucks!
I'm proud of you, buddy.
Did you remember to... hah!
Very good, because i thought
you were gonna be surprised! Okay.
But will you be prepared for...
third surprise?! That one was pretty
obvious, dude. This is gonna be the
greatest date ever! Hey.
Thanks for coming, gumball.
You look... Dressed.
I guess you should come in.
Well, that's one way to get in the house.
Right. So, what do you want
to do today? >> Today is the funeral.
For Mr. cuddles, my pet. Thank goodness.
I thought it might be a real
funeral. I... Mean, pets... pets are
great, like part of the family. So, what
happened to him? My dad flushed him down the
toilet by mistake. That's terrible.
Did he go 'round and 'round
or straight down? Straight down.
I'm penny's father. Wah-hah! Blocked.
Right. Come to the backyard.
The service is about to start.
Penny, I'm sorry.
I thought this was a date.
Why didn't you tell me it was a funeral?
I did, in the corridor at
school. Do you want to come to my house?
It's Mr. cuddles' funeral.
I could use some support from a friend.
Gumball, are you even listening?
This Saturday, 4:00 P.M.
it's... it's a date.
Yeah.
Don't worry.
I'm still here for you, penny.
- >> Thanks, gumball.
- Awesome!
Day for remembering those
who have left us. Shall we go?
Gumball, perhaps you'd
like to say a few words about
Mr. cuddles. O-of course.
Well, Mr. cuddles was penny's
pet. Even though i never met him,
penny's pretty hot, so I'm sure
he was pretty hot, too.
Thank you, gumball.
That was really special. >> My picture!
My sister made a photo tribute so
we can all remember Mr. cuddles.
Aw, how thoughtful.
Want to see? Aaaaaaaaaaah!
A spider! Knock his block off! That's awful!
I hate spiders! Who would want something that
creepy in their house? Ew, ew, ew!
Listen, son, i think it's best you leave.
I'll, let myself
out. >> Play on, dear. ♪ Danny boy ♪
♪ the pipes, the pipes...
♪ sorry. It's me again.
Can i use your bathroom, 'cause it's kind
of a long... it's the second on the left
upstairs. Thanks.
♪ From Glen to Glen ♪ Have a nice funeral!
Just get out of here!
Aw, man, what is wrong with me?
She's never gonna forgive me
for that. I'll spend the rest of my
life alone and never find happiness.
Aaaaaaaaah! A spider!
Knock his block off!
No, wait. >> ♪ but come ye back... ♪ Hey!
I found Mr. cuddles!
He's on the toilet! Is he trying to say
something? He's on the toilet!
Look! The toilet!
Just ignore him. ♪ And white with snow ♪
I guess I'll have to show them. Come here,
little fella. Who's a good spider?
Who's a lovely, good spider?
Good boy, mister... aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Get off, get off, get off,
get off, get off! Aaah! Aaah!
Aaaaaaah! Aah! Aaaaah!
Don't look. You'll just encourage him.
Ha ha!
Aah! Mr. cuddles?
You're back! I thought you were
gone forever! Where did you find him?
In the toilet somewhere.
Gumball, this is amazing.
Yeah, yeah, it's great.
Son, i stand corrected.
I thought you were a good-for-nothing,
young troublemaker, but no, you're...
Yeah, whatever. One question...
is that spider poisonous?
'Cause it just bit me.
Yeah, but it's like a bee sting.
You'd have to be bitten, like,
150 times for it to be dangerous.
Okay, thanks.
If you'll excuse me, I'll go now.
Bye.
He looks real bad. Disgusting.
He looks awful.
He'll never play the clarinet again.
Shh, shh, shh. He's waking up.
Looking good, champ.
Someone's here to see
you, honey. >> Hi, gumball. Hey,
penny. I brought someone
along who wants to say "sorry."
Right, Mr. cuddles?
Come on, you guys! We're gonna be late!
Remind me again exactly why
we're at school on a Saturday.
Are you kidding me? It's club day.
It's the only day of the week when i
get to hang out with people i really like.
What?! Got to go!
Okay... See you all back here at 5:00.
But wait!
I don't have a club to go to!
Well, mom, looks like it's your lucky day.
I'm coming with you to your
anger-management club. That's sweet,
gumball, but behind this door, I'm a very
different person. Trust me, you don't want to see
this. Hello, Nicole. Welcome to... aaach!
Uuuuuh.
Could you guys keep it down a little?
You keep it down!! Hey, anais.
What club are you in?
Physics club. Well, today's your
lucky day, because i...
Let me stop you right there.
You know there are different
types of intelligence? Yeah.
I don't think you have any of them.
I don't get it.
Exactly. Come on! Let me in!
Don't be a club hog!
Fine. Dad, can i join your fantasy club?
Who be therrre? It's me... gumball.
Be you orc? No. Be you dwarf?
No, I'm your son. Be you bearer
of savory snacks for the elders?
What? No. Then begone!
What's up? Man, there's got to
be a club for me somewhere.
You could always join my club.
What is it? Synchronized swimming!
You're good, but i can do better.
Here comes the swan
dive of eternal beauty!
So, how graceful was that?
Dude, you can't swim.
Fair point...
Has anyone seen my trunks? Yeaaah!
Touchdown! >> All right! >> Slam-dunk!
Yeeaaaahh! Hey, guys.
Is this the football club?
Yeeaaahh! Well, did i miss the game?
No, it's going on right out there.
Why aren't you
playing? 'Cause we're the reserve team!
Cool. So, can i join? >> I don't know.
Are you man enough? Me?
I'm at least 50% man.
Well, in that case, here's your towel.
Thanks. So...
Do you guys ever get to play?
Nah, we just hang out here and
act kinda sporty. You guys just take
showers, hang around in towels,
and high-five each other? Heh!
There's a little bit
more to it than that.
Aah! Okay!
Okay, okay!
Hey, Hector, is the game over?
Yeah. We lost. >>.
What?
Aaaahhh! Aah. Aah.
Heh.
Why doesn't anyone want me in their club?
It can't have anything to do
with me... my talent, my intelligence,
or my general awesomeness.
You know what? Too bad for you jealous
people, 'cause I'm starting my own club,
and you are not invited! Okay, I'd like to
welcome everyone to "gumball's club of
gumball." First order of business...
attendance.
Pretty good. Now, it seems like recently
we've been let down by certain... Family
members. So i propose a little exercise
in trust. Okay, don't worry, gumball.
Just close your eyes, let
yourself fall back, and someone will catch
you. Well, I'm a bit scared, gumball.
Well, that's why it's called a
trust exercise. Come on, dude.
Okay.
All in favor of disbanding the club,
say "aye." Aye.
Motion carried. Aw, man.
I'm such a reject.
I wish there was a club for
people like me that no one liked.
I'd join that club in a second.
I wouldn't even care what it was about.
What's going on?
Look no further, fellow loser.
What the...?
We are the unloved, the weird.
Let me introduce you to...
The reject club!
Always accepting new members. Thanks.
I'm desperate, but not that desperate.
No, wait!
We really need new members. We're so bored
of talking to each other, we've been phoning
up the speaking clock for conversation.
If you want, you could be our
president or something. Or...
or... or even better, our king!
Picture this...
gumball watterson, king of the rejects!
What? King of the rejects?
Seriously?
Thanks for the offer, guys, but
it's a "no." King of the rejects.
He rejected us.
And laughed at our loneliness.
Well, we'll see if he's still too good
for us when we've finished with him.
To the nerd-mobile! ♪ nuhn, nuhn,
nuhn, nuhn, nuhn, nuhn, nuhn, nuhn,
nuhn, nuhn, nuhn, nuhn, nuhn, nuhn, nuhn,
nuhn, nuhn, nuhn, nuhn, nuhn, nuhn, nuhn ♪
Rejected, even by my own family!
Look, honey, you're not
a baby anymore. You need to
be able to do things on your own.
There must have been one club
that wanted you. Yeah... the rejects
club. But i politely declined.
Aaaaah! It's okay.
It landed in the vegetables.
Aaaah! The cake! Look...
there's a DVD tied to it.
Greetings, gumball watterson,
from our secret lair.
Isn't that just the library?
Shh! There's more!
So, you think you're too good for us?
Well, you'll soon change your
mind when we upload your embarrassing school
record in a web video hosted by none other
than you. My name is gumball watterson,
and my i.Q. Is smaller than my
shoe size. I wore diapers up till the
age of 11, and i once got detention
for calling miss simian "mum."
Aah! He looks just like you!
Our revenge plan is almost complete.
Uploading.
10 minutes till completion.
Mwa-ha-ha-ha! And... Cut.
How was i? Evil enough? Great.
Now the nerds are bullying me.
I guess you want me to
deal with this on my own. No.
When someone picks a fight with one of us,
they pick a fight with all of us.
Everybody, get in the car.
We've still got time to stop them.
But where is their secret hideout?
It's in the library!
Noooo! It's locked!
My reputation is ruined! No, not yet.
Quick... someone make me angry.
I taped a wrestling match
over our wedding video.
Rrrrrrrrrgggghhhh! Go on without me! Unh!
I'm out of contro-o-o-o-l!
Thou shalt not pass!
You've crossed the wrong
wizard, young man! I am level 40!
Let the battle commence!
Hurrah! I get the first shot.
Meteor sword! Eugh! Ooh!
He's good, but i can't afford to lose.
Magic iron!
Doinggg!
Deflected by the shield of rampor!
Free spell! >>!
You'll have to go without me.
I'm stuck for the next two
turns. Come on!
The computer's just up ahead!
Watch out!
Relax.
It's only bobert. I can take him.
Initiating combat mode.
Aaaaaahhh!
Don't worry, guys. I got this.
- Ehhhhhhhhhhh...
- What are you doing?
Leave it to me. Just go around him.
Are you sure you're gonna be okay?
Don't worry.
The power of physics has never
failed me yet!
The computer!
This is our chance to stop the upload.
30 seconds to completion.
There's a guard! Wsshhh! Wsh! Wsh! Wsh!
Heh-heh-heh-heh-heh.
! That guy looks pretty
dangerous. What are we gonna do?
Leave it to me. Wsh! Wsh! Come on, punk.
Let's dance.
Such grace! The rhythm...
Must... Synchronize! Thanks, buddy.
5 seconds to completion.
Yes! My reputation is safe.
4 seconds till completion.
Aaaah! >> 3 seconds.
2 seconds. 1 second till completion.
Upload complete. Nooooooooooo!
Sending to all school contacts.
My name is
gumball Trisha watterson. That's right...
Trisha is my middle name, and i was born
without eyebrows and need to draw them on
every day. On hot days, i smell like pâté,
and teachers are advised not to
mention it. Also, i have a glandular
problem that causes... Okay! Okay.
You win. I'll join your club.
Are you kidding?
Have you seen your school record?
We're desperate, but we're not
that desperate. Great.
Rejected by the reject club. Well,
that's my reputation ruined until college.
No, it isn't. I counter-hacked the main
school server and rerouted the e-mail
before it got to anyone. Thank you, sis.
Don't worry. We'll always be
there for you. You're part of the
watterson club... Trisha.
Yeah, and whose great idea was that?
What's wrong with it? It's short for
"tristopher." Richard, i thought we
agreed on "Christopher." Christopher,
tristopher... same thing, right?
So, what shall we do with these guys?
Well, i think the
responsible thing to do would be to drive them
home and tell their parents what they've done.
No? Then how about we spray you in
honey and drop you off in
the bear cage at the zoo?
Okay, maybe you'd prefer to
be dropped off naked at the mall?
All those in favor, say "aye." Aye!
Motion carried.