Behold, Darwin... the grossest thing ever!
I shall name it the gross jar!
It will be my legacy to the world!
It's the coolest thing ever.
But i thought my tap-dancing
dolphin impression
was the coolest thing ever.
Yeah, but this just
literally blew you out of the water.
What's inside? Well...
- Choo! - Choo! - Choo!
O-Kay. So, what are you gonna do
with it? Yeah, well, that's the problem.
I don't really know. It needs a final
touch to make it a true masterpiece.
Nuke it!
Could you tell me when my coffee's ready?
I'll be in the garden.
What's going on? It's looking at me!
Dude, where did you
find its eyeball? I-i didn't.
It must be the atomic power of
the microwave. It looks like it's alive.
Mama. Did you hear that?
It called you "mom."
Then i guess that makes you its dad.
Its dad? Aah! What are we gonna do?!
I don't want to be a baby father!
Let's ditch it!
Shh!
don't say stuff like that in front of him!
I mean, come on.
He's kind of cute. Hello, little guy.
Don't you worry about a thing.
Me and your father will take
care of everything. Darwin!
Where do you think you're going?!
Buy some stuff? At the shop?
What are you doing?!
He's your son.
I'm sorry, little guy.
From now on, I'll always be
there for you.
Darwin, i think he's ready
for his first steps. Wait!
Go ahead. Come on. don't be shy.
Come to daddy. Aww!
He's kind of got my eyes.
Don't you think?
Aah! He's got my top lip, too!
Dude, it's what
babies do. He's just suckling.
It's not suckling!
It's eating! Okay, relax.
He's just playing.
He'll come off on his own.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Aah!
His teeth are sinking in!
Okay, that's enough! Bad baby!
Stop mauling your father and
get back in your jar this insta...
Aah! Aah! He's got my neck!
I know what it is.
He must be hungry.
Okay, so it doesn't like fruits, vegetables,
or cereal. But it does like pigeons, rats,
raccoons, seagulls,
and the mailman's butt. What was all that
noise? What are you two up...
aah! What is that thing?!
It's our baby.
What are you talking about?
Where did you find it?
It came out of the microwave.
Are you sure it didn't come
out of the toilet? It's disgusting.
They always look a bit
funny when they're just born.
He's actually very advanced for his age.
You should have seen
him catch that seagull. What?!
You let that monster out?
Look, i was trying to be nice here, but
you better stop insulting our child or i
don't know what I'll do.
It's not a child!
And what is it doing in my high chair?
Don't listen to her, Kenneth.
She's just jealous. You called it
"Kenneth"? Baby needs a name.
Look, like it or not, you're
Kenneth's aunt.
Now, we're gonna buy more pigeon traps.
You babysit. Are you crazy?
Where do you think you're...
I guess you're kind of ugly cute.
What kind of animal are you?
Wow. Those are pretty pointy teeth.
What the... aah!
Kenneth, we're home! What a mess.
Where's anais? Yech. I knew she'd bail.
Gumball, has Kenneth grown? Grown into a
troublemaker. This place is a mess!
Naughty Kenneth.
Parcel for the wattersons.
Hi. Waah! Whoa!
Did Kenneth just eat the mailman?
No, no, no. That's not possible.
Not my Kenneth.
Well, where is he, then?
What do i know...
mailing? I'm more worried about Kenneth.
Does it look to you like he's
gaining weight?
I'm more worried about his attitude.
This boy needs discipline.
I think we need parental advice.
So, um, we're doing this school project.-
And, we've got to look after this,
gross dog thing.
I'm with you.
And we need your help disciplining it.
Okay. It's pretty simple...
kind of like children, actually.
The first thing you have to do is let it know
you're the pack leader, so you look them in the
eyes and tell them
firmly you're the boss.
Now, you've been a naughty doggy!
Dad, he's got your
finger. Well, that's to be expected, son.
The best thing to do is to remain
calm and reassert your authority.
Yeah, but it seems to be eating your arm.
It's just testing its boundaries.
The worst you can do is give it
attention for negative behavior. I have always
found that a positive-reinforcement approach
is the best way to... Dad!
Kenneth's eaten dad!
Probably anais, too!
We've got to save them!
We'll save them later!
Hey, kids. Sorry I'm late.
I... What the...
Mom, something terrible in the garden
became in the microwave and became alive
and swallowed the mailman and dad and anais
and wanted to eat us, and we got here, and...
What? What gumball is
trying to say is the microwave monster
everyone! It's horrible and it's in the
garden and it's really dangerous!
We need to build an army and...
Okay, okay. Slow down, boys.
Where's your father?
It turned into a monster,
and now it's coming to get us!
For goodness' sake. It's probably
just a raccoon. I'll go and check.
You stay here. No! don't go outside!
Richard? Where are you? What's wrong with
the kids? They haven't been this scared
since you made them wax your back.
Richard, you better not be
trying to scare me.
Aww. Richard?
Richard, stop playing games.
Richard? Aaaaaaah!
Mo-o-o-o-o-m! This is all our fault!
It's because we're bad parents! Kenneth
has grown up to be a troubled child.
A troubled child that eats people!
We've got to do something!
You're right. No video games for a week.
Grounded for two weeks?
Okay. Let's send him to boarding school.
Stop being so soft!
We have to stop him now!
What was that? It's an owl.
What was that? A twig.
What was that?
That's my butt cheek quivering with fear.
Really? Yeah. Look.
Aah! Darwin, this is our chance! Yaah!
Are you all right in
there? Partly digested and
a little cramped but otherwise
fine. Just get us out of here, please!
Dude, we got to do something.
I got it! Tie the hosepipe around
me so that all i have to do is dive
into his mouth, grab everyone,
make a human chain...
And when i say, "okay,"
you simply pull us out. Got it? Let's go!
Yeah! Did it! Everybody, hold tight.
Okay, gumball, now pull!
Gotcha! Okay, this isn't working.
Well, think of something else!
Our lives depend on you!
I hate to tell you this,
but i got nothin'.
No, no, no!
Kenneth, please don't eat me! Please!
If you like eating people,
i-I'll bring you some, like a good mother.
And, maybe a salad once in a while because
you're starting to get a little bit chubby.
Here's your package.
Have a nice day. Gumball!
Great idea, turning
on the hose. Pfft. It was nothing.
Just quick thinking, you know?
I-i work best when I'm under pressure.
It definitely wasn't an
accident or anything.
Aww, Kenneth. Look at you now.
You're as sweet as when you were
born.
Who could imagine he'd turn into such a...
Aah! Dad, no! Are you kidding me?!
That thing ate me and barfed me! I'm gonna
end this right now! B-but he didn't mean
it.
It's just that we've been bad parents!
Gumball, that thing is a man-eating
monster! Yes, maybe he eats
people once in a while, but maybe, just
maybe, he needs some love and understanding.
We are responsible for the future
generations. We make the children that will
become the world of tomorrow. don't blame
Kenneth. Blame yourselves, because you're
my parents, too. What?! Look at him.
He won't hurt anyone now. Doesn't
this poor creature deserve a second
chance? Aww! Okay. Trust me, guys...
this time, it'll be different.
On second thought,
we probably should have listened to
dad.
When's someone gonna invent a TV
that flicks its own channels?
Hey, honey. How was work?
Is dinner ready yet?
Hey, mom, dad, guess what!
I got a b-plus in home ec today!
Miss simian said my soufflé was divine.
Yeah. Yeah, that's very interesting.
I also learned how to do a cartwheel.
You guys want to see?
Yeah, yeah. I'm very proud of you, son.
I also crashed your car on the run
from the police after i robbed a bank.
Good for you. Aah! My leg! It's broken!
I probably need to get it cut off!
Aah-haah!
And yet nobody cares.
What do i have to do to get
noticed in this house?! Ooh! What?
Richard,
i think gumball needs some attention.
Maybe you should go and play catch.
Yeah, yeah, we're all
very proud of you, Nicole.
What?
Listen, honey, I'm sorry you've not
been getting enough attention lately.
I'm going to make it up
to you starting tomorrow.
Why not now?!
So, penny, want to hang out after school?
I'll show you my cartwheel. I've seen it.
It's not as good as it sounds.
Sorry, gumball.
It's cheerleader tryouts tonight.
I've been practicing all year for this.
Another time, though.
Okay. No problem. I love you, penny.
What? What? Nothing.
I just said i love peanuts.
Yeah, peanuts. They taste so good.
Gumball, i am a peanut.
That's like me saying i like to eat cats.
Maybe you should think twice
about the things you say.
But i did think twice.
Well, maybe you need to think three times.
Anyway, see you later.
Wait! I didn't say, "peanuts"!
I said, "ponies"! I love ponies!
They taste of nuts!
Whatever. Maybe you need
to talk with your mouth shut.
Is that really the way you talk to girls?
Mom?! What are you doing here?!
Well, you said you
wanted more attention, so i followed you
to school. But by the looks of it, you need
more than attention.
You need serious help, little man.
Aw, mom, if you're seriously going to
follow us around all day, do you really
need to hold my hand?
Yes. Yay! Mom's at school!
And it's not all day. It's all week.
I took the night shift.
Hey, mom, need a diaper for that baby?
Ooh, actually, i am fully potty trained,
so check your facts, all right?
You know you got them good
when their voices go high.
Gumball, are you really gonna take that?
She just owned you. What?
You got a better idea?
Well, first of all, drop an octave.
Then give her a taste of her own
medicine. Try this.
Tina, I'd just like to say that maybe
you only bully people because you're
insecure about your walnut-sized brain and
the fact that you smell like a sweaty butcher.
I'll have you know that
smell is a glandular problem!
"Glandular." Wow.
It actually worked. Yeah, that was funny.
But good luck when Tina comes
back and your mom's not around to
hold your hand. don't worry, gummy-puss.
I'll hold your hand until college
if i have to. "Gummy-puss."
Mom, stop embarrassing me! >> it burns!
My eyes! What was that?!
I don't know... paint?
Aah! My hair! What was that?
Chlorine from
the pool? Unh! Aah!
What was that? Fertilizer?
I guess it's all right, then.
But that's still two hours of detention
for potentially damaging my beautiful face.
Really, principal brown,
you need to be firmer than that.
- >> - O-okay.
- Four hours' detention.
Eight hours? Good.
See you in detention, watterson.
Mom, you're not helping.
The nerds think you look like a
dodeca-dork with your mom at
school. What does that mean?
It's a 12-sided dork, honey.
Mom, you're not helping.
Mom, you're not helping!
Whoo-whoo! Come on, honey.
Open the tunnel for the choo-choo train.
Mom, you're not
help... Enough!
The Tina thing was kind of helpful,
but this has gone too far!
Wait a minute. I... Thanks.
Now, seriously, i need you to stop
meddling with my life! I'm not meddling.
I'm helping. Helping by meddling.
You're just a big meddler!
I'm not a meddler.
I'm your mother! And a meddler.
Hey! Isn't that the girl you like?
Mom, no! Excuse me, penny.
Have you got a second?
Sure. You guys will need to be quick.
The cheerleader tryouts are
about to start. Mom, if you love me,
please don't do this.
Come on, gummy-puss. don't be shy.
My baby has something to say to you.
No, i don't.
He'd like to take you out on a date.
That's not true. He loves you. >> Really?
No, i don't!
I don't love penny, and i never will!
Gumball!
Well, thanks for being honest with me.
No, wait! I meant I'll never love peanuts!
No... ponies!
See what you did?! You upset penny!
How am i supposed to get her back?!
Well, you know, i could
help you with that. That's enough!
Okay? That's enough!
I'm my own man now! I make my own
decisions, and i don't need you babying me
anymo... anymo...
Thanks. Now, just go home, okay? Come on.
We all had a great time.
Didn't we, Darwin? To be honest, I've
never been so embarrassed in
my entire life! Why are you smiling,
then? Well, at first,
i was trying not to hurt your
feelings, but now I'm just stuck! I
beg of you, just get out of my life.
Okay.
I guess I'll just go home, then.
Mom, you've got to come back!
I made my own decision!
It was a bad one...
a really, really bad one! Thank goodness
she's gone.
I'll never smile again. Darwin!
Mom, you're back! Yay!
Do you know where your
brother is? In the changing room. Thanks.
Gumball, it's me.
Open the door. No! No, i won't!
What happened? It's awful.
I made a decision on my own, and
it was bad. Listen, whatever it
is you've done, you need to come
out and face it. All right.
All right. I'm coming out.
You were gonna try and get
closer to penny by joining her
cheer team, but now you feel embarrassed
because you have to wear a skirt.
What?! No! I'm gonna beat penny
at her own game so she'll realize how
awesome and manly i am.
Then she'll definitely want to date me.
Right. So, what's the problem?
The problem is me!
What if I'm not as good as the
other girls?! What if they laugh at me?!
And this leotard makes me look fat,
so i put this skirt on to hide my butt.
What exactly do you want me to do, honey?
Hello?
Be there, of course?
I need emotional support. You're my mom.
Start acting like it. Okay, let's go.
♪ Hey! ♪ ♪ hey! ♪ ♪ here we go ♪
♪ hey! ♪ ♪ hey! ♪ ♪ here we go ♪
♪ hey! ♪ ♪ hey! ♪
Tsk, tsk, tsk. Now, penny,
i have to say, I'm a little disappointed.
I know. It's just i had some
emotional problems this afternoon...
you leave your emotions at the door!
This is cheerleading, not drama
club! You better shape up or ship out,
'cause this is the big leagues,
sister, and right now you're at the bottom of
the barrel! Is there anything you'd like to
add, principal brown? Only that
we're making cuts today, and after that
performance, someone's going to have
to be pretty bad for it not to be you.
Am i too late?
- No!
- Mom...
Well, it's a no for me, Mr. small.
It's a no for me, too.
That's two nos, gumball.
You're going home. No!
Mom, make them recount the score!
Make them recount the score!
Well, zero plus zero equals zero, honey.
Why is the world so
cruel?! Don't worry.
You'll do better next time...
After a couple of years' intense training.
gumball, thank you!
It was so brave of you to sacrifice
your dignity so i can get on the team.
I guess that means you do like me.
Just a little?
Peanuts. Ponies.
I think that means "yes."
Mom, you know when i
said i wanted to be my own man
and make my own decisions? Yes.
Can it just wait for a few years?
The longer, the better,
honey. Even when you're 80,
you'll still be my gummy-puss.