You know what?
I don't think I'm gonna wear this anymore.
Why? I thought it brought you good luck.
Yeah, it does, but
nothing's fun anymore.
See? Watch this.
Whoa! Ta-da. Whoop-de-boring-do.
What are you talking
about?!
That was fan-flapping-tastic!
Yeah, a week ago,
maybe, but now it's just lame.
I think I'm gonna throw it out.
Don't throw it out!!
I could really use some luck
right now.
I've been trying to get on
"win or don't win" for five
months, but they're not
returning my calls.
You're never gonna get
on that show, hat or no hat.
There's a show called "hat or no hat"?
Look, you want it? You have it.
Hello? Would i?! Tomorrow?!
Thank you,
"win or don't win"!
Wow! This hat is amazing!
Okay, guys, as
impressive as all this is,
let's not get carried away.
There's no way a tinfoil hat is
responsible for...
Richard! What are you...
Hello?
Interview? Tomorrow?
For a promotion and a pay rise?!
What was that?
That was the sound of
doom for the wattersons.
Do you ever miss your helmet?
No. Why?
Well, everyone seems
to be using it for really cool
stuff, like dad with the TV show
or mom with her job.
All you ever did was lame party
tricks. It doesn't matter, Darwin.
I'm happy to see the back of it.
Succeeding at everything really
took the joy out of life.
Besides...
Sometimes in life, you make your
own luck!
It's so good to fail again.
You see, you take a pinch of
success, a dash of failure, you
mix it together, and that's what
makes life int...
See? That wasn't so bad.
You just blew up the ant farm.
It's okay! Aah!
Life is great, Darwin! So, you're saying
you're happy when you fail?
Absolutely.
It's the struggle that makes a
victory sweet.
Besides, i still got it.
Aaaah!
Butter side down, just like
poor uncle Eddie.
What do you know...
my lunch is on the floor.
Hey, who's the funny guy who did
that?
And you
know what the best thing about failure is,
Darwin? No.
Is that it builds your sense of humor.
Who am i kidding?
I'm nothing without my helmet!
I want it back!
I need it!
But i need it more,
'cause i need to win the show!
Well, i need it to get
the promotion, which is more
important than a game show.
But if i win the show,
I'll get a speedboat!
Think about how great it would
be for me!
Richard, you'll never
use it.
Nicole, if i win a
speedboat, I'm gonna use it.
You have to understand,
I'm doing this for the greater
good.
Winning the speedboat will be
good for you but not for the
rest of the family... You're right.
I'm sorry, Nicole.
I-i don't know what came over
me.
It's okay.
Just, where did you hide the
helmet?
It's in this bag.
No, wait!
Actually, it's in... it's in
this one.
I was gonna trick you.
I'm sorry.
I guess that helmet's got more
power over me than i thought.
Thanks for being honest,
honey.
That was an astonishing
interview.
There's... Just one thing.
You are aware that
if you get the job, you won't be
able to wear that papier-mâché
helmet, right?
Of course. But for the record, it's not
papier-mâché. It's tinfoil. >> no.
I'm pretty sure it's
papier-mâché painted gray.
What?
Can i switch your TV on?
Sure?
And he's won the speedboat!
Yay!
This isn't going to affect my
chances, is it?
Um, what do you think? It's mine!
No, mine!
Give it back! Give it back!
It's mine!
I lost my job for it! It's mine!
I need it!
But I'm on "hat or no
hat" tomorrow!
Give... It... Back!
Stop it!
Look at what you've become!
This stupid hat is driving you
crazy! Actually, it's a helmet.
It's not a helmet or a
hat!
It's a piece of tinfoil!
And it's tearing this family
apart!
Look at you!
You're behaving like animals!
Anais is right.
That helmet has such a grip on
us.
It's like its magic is
taking control of the person who
wears it.
Ha!
Well, since none of you guys
want it, i guess i can have it
back.
No!
Me and Darwin have been talking,
and we've decided it has to be
destroyed. What?! You can't destroy it!
I'm nothing without it!
I'm sorry, honey, but
anais is right.
Can... can i have one more go? No!
Don't touch it!! Hey! No! No! No!
It's mine! Aah! Aah! No! It's my helmet!
Dude, chill out.
It's just a bucket with some
tinfoil on it.
Aaah! Give it back!
It's my helmet!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Why can't we just put
it in the bin?
Because they'll just
pull it out again.
We have to take it to the bin of
all bins... the dump.
Can't we just rip it
up?
Have you ever tried
ripping up tinfoil?
Sounds horrible.
What are we gonna do
with it, then?
Throw it in the
garbage crusher.
Can you hear that? What? That noise.
Sounds like a cat trying to say
"snake."
Snake.
It's probably just the wind. Maybe.
I don't know what the big deal
with this lucky helmet is,
anyway.
Looks pretty normal to me.
Look... a gold ring!
Look... a pearly necklace!
Wow!
A diamond-encrusted chain!
And it spells "Darwin"!
Come on. We're nearly there.
I-i can't do it, anais.
It's... it's too heavy.
Well, give me the
helmet.
I'll deal with it.
No!
It's a man's job.
You're... you're just a little
girl. The helmet is my burden to carry.
You can carry me, though!
There. I've done my part.
Now you do yours.
Throw the stupid thing in the
crusher.
Okay!
Well, good riddance!
Darwin, look out!
Give
me my helmet!
The helmet's mine! Give it back!
Give it! Give it!
Dude, what's wrong
with your voice?
I just really need to cough.
Better. Aha! No!
Give it up, gumball! There's two of us!
You'll never win! Yeah?
I can already feel its power!
Well, not for long!
Come on, Darwin.
You'll never hit me!
I'm the luckiest man alive!
It's not luck!
It's just we can't throw very
well!
Then let me make it
easy for you.
Come on, anais!
There's no way you can miss from
there!
Nice try, but now it's my turn.
Look... a tennis-ball machine.
Good luck finding a power supply
for that.
Look... a
generator.
Okay, maybe the hat is
magic after all.
Run!!
He's got us cornered!
What are we gonna do?!
Pass me that stale
baguette. Why? don't you worry about
it. Just tell mom and dad i love them.
What? Darwin, no!
- No!
- No! My power!
Come on, Darwin!
He lost the helmet!
Cool.
No! No! No, no! No!! Gumball!!
Almost... Got... It. What the...
what is wrong with you?!
My helmet...
I can almost reach it.
Give me your hand! No! I need the power!
For goodness' sake,
man!
It's only a piece of tinfoil!
But think of all the
stuff we could do with it. Yes! Ha ha!
Okay, you can pull me up now.
Listen, gumball, the
helmet is powerful, but it's
also evil.
Look at what it's
done to you and mom and dad!
But... but without
it, I'm nothing!
Gumball, we're nothing
without you. So, give me your other hand.
Whoo.
Yay!
Richard, are you sure
this is a good idea?
Of course, honey.
I said I'd use it, didn't i?
How far away
is the sea?
About 100 miles.
And welcome to the welterweight title.
You okay? Yep.
School was awesome today!
I was hanging out with Tina.
She taught me how to donate to
charity. Who is this for, again? >> Me.
Then she helped tear through my homework.
And finally, we had
lunch together.
What should i try first?
Lasagna. It was great!
What? I think you're being bullied.
Nah. We're just having fun... Nope.
You're definitely getting bullied.
What am i gonna do?!
Don't worry, bro.
I'll take care of this for you.
Hey, Tina, you've been picking
on my brother, and i think it's
time you guys talked about this
face-to-face.
Tomorrow? 4:00 P.M.?
Behind the school?! No, wait!
That's not what i meant! Oopsie.
Well? Looks like your
face-to-face turned into more of
a... Face-to-fist.
What the...
what?!
I think she wants to
have a fight with you.
He's out cold! Come on, son.
It's time i showed you how to
deal with bullies.
There comes a point in every
man's life where he has to stand
up for himself.
But that's okay, 'cause daddy's
here to teach you an old family
technique that got me out of
trouble many times.
Oooh. A secret fighting technique? Yes.
It's called...
The bunny hop.
But remember, you must never use
it in anger.
I promise, father.
All right.
You be the bully.
Okay.
Come on. don't be shy.
Try to take my lunch money.
Aah! don't hurt me!
Not the face!
Here's my lunch money... and my
lunch!
Please, take it!
Please, please, please!
That was step one.
And here comes the bunny hop.
Hah.
Blblblblblblblblblblblblbl!
Well, that wasn't
much help.
You're right.
I think you need help from a
real adult.
So, school counselor.
Pretty scary title?
But don't you worry your tiny,
little heads about it.
Think of me as a friend, a
compadre, a fellow pilgrim on a
mad journey we call...
Life.
So, tell me, what's shakin'?
I'm fine.
No, he's not! He's being bullied! >>.
The big "b," You know,
more often than not, conversation beats
confrontation. Hands down.
Let's meditate on this.
Ohmmmmmmm.
Ohmmmmmmmmmmm.
So, tell me, who's bullying
you?
Tina Rex.
Tina Rex?!
Don't tell her you saw me!
Well, that wasn't much
help.
No way!
Gumball's gonna fight Tina?
She's gonna mash him!
He's toast!
She's gonna skin him alive!
This will be the greatest
fight ever! This is getting out of hand.
Don't worry. I'll fix this. Come on!
What is wrong with you guys?
How many of you have been
bullied by Tina?
Maybe. >> I guess. >> I have.
Don't you realize if
we all join forces, we can stand
up to Tina once and for all?
And no student will ever be
bullied again!
Yeah! We can also stop global warming!
Yeah! And bring peace to the world!
Yeah!
And build schools for
the dolphins in the rainforests
so they can cure baldness! Yeah! Anais?
Sorry, gumball!
The power's gone to my head!
See you on capitol hill!
Good luck with the fight, man!
There you are. Darwin!
You're supposed to be here when
your best friend's about to get
mangled by...
Shhhhhhhhhhhh! Just follow me!
Behold my super bully protection
suit of power!
Whoa!
I love it! Pshooo!
Looking good.
Now, check this out.
It's got bouncy bubble wrap
pants, and it has an mp3 player
as standard.
And that's not all.
This string here operates the
super counterattack device.
No, wait!
You've only got one shot, so you
must wait for the right moment.
Okay.
And last but not
least, the tassels!
What do these do?
Move your arm around.
Oooooh.
Tassels.
Okay.
Time to put it to the test.
Ready? Okay.
Can you feel anything yet? Aah!
Okay.
I'll keep going.
Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
What did it feel like?
What?
Like I'm being hit with a stick.
That wasn't much help.
That's okay.
We can rebuild it better,
faster, stronger!
Let's get to work! Too late.
You know what? Maybe it won't be so bad.
I'll just meet Tina in a quiet,
calm atmosphere, and we'll talk
things through like civilized
people. Yeah! This is a great
idea! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
This is a terrible
idea.
What's going on here?
I'll have no fighting on my
watch.
Gumball watterson.
I might have known.
Thank you, miss simian!
I was gonna fight a t-Rex.
Please send me to detention.
Well, i suppose i could...
after my coffee break.
But, miss simian,
Tina...
coffee break. But, miss simian,
you're my last hope! Please!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Where's gumball?
Here.
What am i gonna do?
What am i gonna do?!
Use the
bunny hop, son.
Son. Son. Son. Son.
Dad?
What are you doing here?
Well, i wasn't gonna miss the big fight.
Gumball!
Time to deal with
this like a man.
Blblblblblblblblblbl! Gumball!
Stop running! Dude, i have no idea what
- you're saying.
- Sorry!
Aaaaah!
Aaaah! >> Gumball!
Sorry.
Man! Sorry.
Sorry. Aaaah!
Ha ha! Scaredy-cat!
Mr. small! Please! Let me in!
Aaah! No! Please!
Let me in! >> No! Mr. small!
Go away! Aaaaaah!
Would you mind removing
your glasses when you're at the
table?...Yes?
What happened to you?!
I... Ran into a door?
That's not true.
He's being bullied!
Seriously, i did run into a door.
Mom! Calm down! I'm perfectly calm!
I just need a word with Mr. Rex,
honey-pie.
Gumball!
Sit!
You guys make up!
Mr. Rex. Hi, Mr. Rex.
We need to talk about your daughter.
So, it's going to be
like that, is it?
Well, that's fine by me!
Your dad is pretty scary. So's your mom.
Tina? Is it true that you're bullying me?
What? No!
I thought we were just having
fun.
So, why were you
chasing me?
I only wanted to speak to
you, but you ran away.
Everyone thinks I'm a brute,
just like my dad. But I'm not!
I don't think you're a brute. >> Really?
Of course.
You're just a dangerous friend
with a terrifying amount of
strength. >> Thanks! Come on.
Give me five... How about a friend hug?
Too... Friendly!
Well, I'm glad we finally
reached an agreement.
Goodbye, Mr. Rex.
So, everything's okay
between you and Tina?
Yep! Everything's just fine.