I think lunch is the best,
because you've already had breakfast...
But you still have
dinner to look forward to.
A plastic magic wand!
Sweeeet! Make a wish!
I wish i had six eyes.
One... Two...
Maybe you have to wave it.
I wish gumball had six eyes. One...
Two...
Aw, this magic wand is weak. Magic wand?
Can i have a turn?
Sure, but it doesn't really...
Cool! With this,
i can make all my wishes come true.
My first wish is that this wand doesn't
turn out to be a big fraud, like that stupid
wishbone! What wishbone?
Well, when i was a boy
about your age...
I wish that the sausages
would fly into my mouth!
Mom, i made a wish on the wishbone, and
nothing happened! What did you think, that it
was gonna come true? Magic isn't real.
You mean, it's... A fraud? Yeah.
It's a fraud. AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-
AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-
AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA... AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-
and i didn't stop screaming for 15 years.
AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA...
AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA... AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA!
AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA!
I never believed in anything again.
But i believe this will be different.
Now, I've got some wishing to
do! You know what this
means, Darwin. We have to make
sure all of dad's wishes come true.
Why? Because if we don't,
he'll never be able to believe
in anything again.
And he might go crazy and start screaming.
We have to make sure he
thinks that wand is real. Yeah!
I wish for sausages to fly into
my mouth.
Whoo-oo-oo-oo-oo.
Ptuh!
I think you and me are gonna be friends.
Ha-ha! I wish the sink was fixed.
Well, how do you fix
the sink? I don't know. Aaaaaaahh!
Quick! Mr. dad's gonna
find out the wand's not real!
Aaah.
Ptuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuh! Ptuh!
Ptuh! Buh-b-b-b-b-b-b-b!
Bah-b-b-b-b! Pweh!
You are truly powerful.
I shall name you... Wanda...
the wonderful wand of wonder!
Quick... i think dad's gonna make
another wish. I wish it was raining
pancakes!
Ooooh.
I wish it was Christmas every
day.
Ho-ho-ho!
Merry Christmas, everyone!
Oooh! I wish...
I wish i was taller.
Hee-hee! Hee-hee! Now I'm a giant!
I wish... I wish i had a monster truck.
Yeah, a monster-truck t-shirt.
Heh-heh! Heh!
I wish... I wish i could be invisible.
Come on, Darwin.
Just do what i do. Where's dad?
I wonder where he's gone.
Look...
he left his wand floating in midair.
He's here. Come on, Darwin.
Let's go and find him.
But he's here. Darwin! I wish...
I wish i wasn't so hot. Ooh!
Ooh! Ooh! Aah! Whoo! Aah!
Not again.
Mr. watterson!
Would you kindly refrain from
offending my wife's eyeballs with
your public display of vulgarity?
Sorry, Mr. Robinson. Hey.
Wait a second.
You picked the wrong day to mess with...
The bunny warlock!! Sorry...
what? If it's a fight you
want, it's a fight you've got! But i think i
should warn you... i have supernatural powers!
The only thing supernatural
about you is your ignorance.
I wouldn't be laughing if i was facing...
The mighty bunny warlock!!
The only thing mighty
about you is your ignorance.
I used the same joke again. Perhaps
you haven't noticed my magic wand and...
My cape! >> You don't have a cape.
I wish for a cape. You look ridiculous.
You leave me no choice,
sir. I wish... I wish...
Here we go. I wish you looked ridiculous!
Aah! Horrible! Take it off! Take it off!
Cover your eyes, woman!
Aah! No! Put it back on!
Put it back on!
And i wish your wife's head was a melon.
Now i wish you would
fly away out of my sight.
Aaah!
You dared to doubt the all-powerful
bunny warlock! I can't hold it any
longer! Now, begone!
He really is a wizard.
Run, Margaret, run! Aah! He! He-he!
A-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha! Mr. dad's turning evil.
Maybe it's time we told him the truth.
But if we tell him
the truth, he's gonna get upset,
like when he was a boy. You're right.
I know!
We're gonna have to take the wand back!
Is there nothing you can't do, Wanda?
I think i finally understand
your true power! I wish...
I wish... I w... This has gone on
long enough. Hmph!
What are you doing here?
This wand... it has made you evil.
We're taking it back.
Hmph! You think that you
mere mortals have the power to
challenge me? Come...
take the wand if you dare.
Slip-over spell! We've got to do it.
It'll break his heart if he
finds out. Aaaah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Can't you see what
you've become?
I can see perfectly clearly.
I have become a master wizard!
- Slow-motion spell!
- It's power has overtaken you.
Reverse spell!
You overtaken has power it's!
No, it's more like ouy
nekatrevo sah rewop s'ti!
Love spell!
Inside-out spell!
Gross! Back-to-normal spell!
H-ha-ha-ha-ha! Give us the wand!
Never! I wish your face was his
butt and his butt was your face!
Really? I wished it, didn't i?
A-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Now i wish that your butt was
his face and his face was your butt!
Naaaaaaa-ha-ha! I wish that, um, your
face was kissing his butt and his butt
- was kissing your face!
- A-ha-ha!
This has got to stop. AAA-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Dad! We've got something to tell you.
What's going on?
Why have you stopped? That wand's a fake.
It's just a plastic toy, free
from a cereal packet.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha! What nonsense!
If that's true, how do you explain this?
Yaaaaa...
It was us. We've been making
it happen right from the start.
I hope you're not mad at us. You mean
you two kids spent the whole day making
incredible wishes come true?
You did that all for me? Of course!
Even when i made your butt kiss his face and
his face kiss your butt, you did that for
- me?
- Come here and give me a
big hug. Mmmmmm. But hang on.
If you were making my wishes come true,
doesn't that mean that Wanda the wonderful wand
of wonder is a fraud? Yeah.
A fraud?
Yaa-AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA-AAA...
It's mine! The power is all mine!
I wish you didn't have
that ridiculous haircut.
I wish i hadn't said that.
Aaah!
Careful, numbskull! These trophies are
a symbol of my excellence as a teacher.
It took me 754 years to collect them all.
What was that?! Hello!
"Favorite teacher award"?
It's like the best one and stuff,
but you'll never win it. Why not?
Because you need a letter of recommendation
from a student who... Actually likes you.
That sounds easy enough.
Seriously, though, no one likes
you, miss simian... not even me!
And i like everybody. Nobody likes me?
Dude, i think something's
wrong with miss simian.
What makes you say that? She hasn't told
anyone off all day.
[ Music blaring, laughter,
[ indistinct shouting ] That is weird.
Whoo-hoo! Hey, guys! Wait up!
Gumball? Yeah...?
You and i are friends, right?
Are we? Well, what with all
the detentions and everything, i
guess we spend a lot of time together...
I guess so.
Anyway, gotta go. Just one more thing.
Would you mind if i hang out
with you just for a little while?...Yeah.
Yeah, i would.
Basically, she asked to be my friend.
Well, i told her "no," obviously.
But now she's just following me
around. And the strangest thing is,
she's completely unresponsive.
Watch. See? Nothing!
Try something hot. Is she still there?
Yep.
Shoo! Shoo! Shoo!! Fetch!
I hope things get better tomorrow.
What is she doing in my house?
I'm sorry. I just thought that maybe
we could share a nice breakfast
together, but since you all hate me,
I'll just go. I'm walking.
It's so sad. This is me...
On my way. I'm at the door.
This is kind of harsh. I'm turning
the doorknob. I'm opening the door.
I don't know why, but I'm crying!
Boy, it sure looks lonely out
there.
Mom, why do you hate miss simian so much?
I don't want to talk about it.
Please let her stay! Okay.
She can stay, but...
thank you!
You're such a kind and friendly family!
You know, I've never had friends before.
I don't even know what friends
do. Don't worry. We'll show you.
Now, a very important part of friendship
is sharing. Imagine you both have ice
creams. But what's this?
Darwin has dropped his ice cream.
I said, "Darwin has dropped his
ice cream." Splat!
You got it on my shoes.
Do you want to share
mine? Very good.
Ice cream, Darwin? Aw, thanks!
But, gumball, you don't have
an ice cream. Want to share mine? Sure.
Dude, this is so gross! Why don't you
pretend you have your own ice cream?
Why didn't i think of that?
Friends also high-five, like
this. High-five! Okay, now...
No, i meant slap my...
Let's move on to the next lesson.
How about we all play a game,
like friends do?
Here's one we made up. It's called...
Dodge or dare!
Roll the dice. Take a card.
What'd you get? "Put a gooey
hair ball in miss simian's lunch."
L-let me take that. Pick another.
"When miss simian's back is turned..."
A-actually, let me pick one for you.
"cover simian in slug juice,
drop water balloons on simian,
miss simian, miss simian, miss simian..."
heh heh. Forget the cards. Here's a dare.
Make the most annoying noise
possible. >> Eeeh... O... Kay.
That was... Good, but we know that
you can do better. Like when you're mad
at us. >> you mean this little thing?
Gu-u-u-u-mba-a-a-a-ll!! That... Was...
- Awesome!
- High-five!
That still needs a little work.
I've got my eye on you, simian.
Do it again! Do it again!
I'm so pleased to finally
have such great friends!
We love you, miss simian. Sorry, kids.
Miss simian, c-can i have a word
with you in private, please?
Yes, Nicole, how can i help you?
Listen, simian, you might have the
rest of them fooled, but i don't trust you
for a second. I remember you from school.
I remember the horrible name you
used to call me every day.
Do you remember that? Yes, i do.
And I'm sorry. What?
I was that horrid person for
so long, and look where it got me.
No friends, no family... just
bitterness and wrinkles. But even an old ape
can change. Will you give me that chance?
I don't know. It's all happening so fast.
Ple-e-e-e-e-ase?
Okay, I'll... I'll give it another shot.
What do we do now, best friends?
Let's see.
I know! Best friends write letters
to each other about how great they
are. Wow! What a... Friendly idea.
What shall we write? Um...
Ooh... How about "we, the
aforementioned, unanimously agree that miss
simian is worthy of this year's 'favorite
teacher' award."
"Favorite teacher award."
Okay! Done it! It's mine!
- A! Ha-a!
- A!
Look how happy she is.
That's the power of
friendship. Wow! You baked that cake for
miss simian? Yeah.
I think she deserves a second
chance. Is miss simian around? Nah, dude.
She just drove off.
You should have seen her, all
dancing and laughing, saying she finally got
some losers to write her a "favorite teacher"
nomination.
What was the word she used? >> "Losers."
Unh! Heh! Nice first steps, loser! Unh!
Nice cycling, loser! Nice "poem," loser!
Nice hair, loser. Nice husband, loser!
Everyone, get back in the car.
Now? Soon, the trophy will be mine.
Aaaah! We'll see about that,
you two-faced baboon! There's
nothing you can do about it, loser!
Mom! What are you doing?!
Something i should have
done a long time ago.
Kids, throw stuff at her! But isn't that
dangerous? Not as dangerous
as disobeying your mother!
Sorry! >> Aaah! Open your mouth.
Aah! I hope you like
pepperoni! >> Aaaaaah! Aaaah!
That was close. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhh!
Cool! Not coo-o-o-o-l! I thought you were
our friend, miss simian. Ha!
Who needs friends when you have
this letter? Aah!
There it is, Richard! Get it!
Do what?! I'll get closer,
and you lean in and grab it.
Seriously? Little bit closer, honey!
Ooh! Almost... There! Aah! Dad!
Oooh-whoo! Whoo-oooh! Hold on! Waaah-ha!
Hi. >> Bye!
Aaaaaaaah!
Got it! Ha ha! Aaaaaah!
Whoooooa! Never... Trick...
My... Family... Again!
Mom, watch out!
Aaah!
And that, kids, is why you wear
seatbelts. Where's miss simian? >>...
Hey! Miss simian, no!
You could still be friends with
us if you like.
Nah! Aaaaaaaaaah!
What did i miss?
Dad! Just simian taking a little tumble.
Maybe that'll teach her
for "monkeying around."
We shouldn't laugh. She may be
seriously hurt. Well, you shouldn't have
"gibbon" her a second chance. No, really.
That's enough. Well, she shouldn't
have "orangu-tangled" with us.
I said that's enough.
That was so worth it.